Chapter 13: Bonus: War

Does the end justify the means? That is possible. But what will justify the end? To that question, which historical thought leaves pending, rebellion replies: the means.

-Albert Camus, The Rebel

≡≡≡Ω≡≡≡

Nurmengard, Győr-Moson, Hungary

April 30th, 1945 C.E.

Reg Hig had been afraid all throughout the war against Grindelwald. It was a deep and abiding fear that sat in his stomach like a stone, soured his mouth into a grimace, and left him checking and re-checking the wards compulsively. But he went anyway. He was scared and he was always exhausted and he would sometimes vomit in nervous heaves until his mouth burned with bile, but he went anyway.

If he'd had a choice, he probably wouldn't have gone. But he'd been compelled by pride and ambition, and so he had volunteered with forty other Americans to join the war against the mad Hungarian. It was the only way he could have a future in the Council. Even at that time, he'd led a sizeable contingent of the egalitarian wing, but it was clear that no coward could ever rise to great power. His father's generation had proven their mettle against centaurs and giants in the west, serving as rangers over vast swaths of territory to enforce the Statute of Secrecy. But those days were past, thanks to vigilance and genocides. So in Hig's time, mighty heroes fought Dark Lords and Ladies. Gellert Grindelwald was the darkest of Dark Lords anyone had ever seen, untouchable in his mastery and unstoppable in his cruelty. If Hig had failed to volunteer, it would have been a black mark on the family name.

But he was afraid, and had been since the moment he'd read about the Anschluss - when he'd realized the shape of things to come. And he'd known from the start, even then, that it would do no good to try to hide it. And so he'd owned it.

Before the raids and with every battle, he'd proclaimed his own terror to his allies. Hig had shouted out his fear, and then said he was going to fight anyway. If he could do it, then by Mukwooru's toe, they could damn well join him and fight by his side. Fear meant nothing, he would declare, and then he would roar out about all the things they were trying to preserve, and roar about the twisted villainy of Grindelwald's "greater good." He would roar for them to follow him, and then they would leap to their broomsticks and surge into the air and their hearts would sing with fire.

Today had been different.

After the plans had been made, and he'd shaken hands with Albus and Fu-min and Dominique and Astrid, Hig had turned to the Westphalians and Argentines and Brazilians, all of whom were now under his command, and he had said nothing. He'd just looked each of them in the eye in turn. When you needed to say something good and true - when you needed the best words - he'd long ago learned that each person had to write those words for themselves. Hig met their gazes, and looked at them steadily for a meaningful moment, and he knew that they each found their own song. And he had found that there was no longer any fear in his own heart. There was just a deep calm.

Even Limpel Tineagar had been solemn and appreciative today, and she was the most annoying witch he'd ever met. Normally, no plan was good enough for her, no leader was smart enough for her, and no speech was inspiring enough for her. He'd barely known her when they left for Europe last year, having spoken to the tall, half-blooded witch only during Council debates, and he almost wished that was still true. She took nothing on faith, and she never seemed to stir with a flicker of passion. But today she had clasped his hand and kissed him on the cheek.

Today they were all heroes, and that would be true even if they didn't see tomorrow.

Hig was flying at the rear of the ragged formation, high over Hungary. They'd started off in a neat V, but it had degraded to a shapeless mass as they struggled to keep up with Momo. Momo was the pacer, and so he had to keep up a steady and unflagging maximum speed on his broom. Three hours and twelve minutes of flight from their Austrian origin should bring them directly over Nurmengard… but only if Momo kept at top speed.

Clouds blew past, above and below. A dense floor of puffy cumulonimbus anvils and a wispy ceiling of cirrus scratchings. Hig wondered if you could practice neladoracht from within the clouds, and if so, what their fortunes would be today. This would be a day of beginnings and endings… but whose beginning, and whose ending?

They were something like twenty thousand feet above the ground, breathing easily and staying warm with magical assistance, but Hig was still relieved when Momo brought his broom to a swift halt. Most of the Americans overshot him and had to swing back around. They gathered around Momo, many flexing stiff fingers or shifting in their perches.

Two groups of six separated out from the rest, sorting themselves into Aleph Group and Beth Group. The others divided themselves into groups of twelve: Gimel and Daleth Groups. It was difficult to speak - something about the way the sound traveled through the intervening air between two Bubblehead Charms distorted it badly - but it had all been arranged beforehand at Dumbledore's direction. The Americans were here to destroy the Dogs, and so very much depended on their success.

At Hig's hand signal, all four groups shifted their positions and began swooping downwards in widespread formations, and the assault was on.

It took about fifteen minutes to descend. Several of them kept up protection spells, while others worked on keeping them as hidden as possible, while still others tried to pry a clear way through the detectors as they were encountered. They met success in all three tasks - not surprising, considering the assembled might of the American expeditionary force and their careful preparation for the day's attack.

Soon, Nurmengard was in sight, jutting into the sky at them like an accusing finger. The fortress was a single thick tower of black stone, square and solid, topped with a ziggurat. It was built into the face of a cliff, overlooking wide plains of grass. Giant natural statues of karst from Bükk sat lumpily in the fields around Nurmengard; the bulbous grey rock formations might normally have been beautiful, but in this context they seemed eerie and organic.

Hig's gaze was drawn to a sky-platform that hung in the air over the fortress. There was a guard, and Hig saw when the man noticed them. Curses rained down and took the sentry down, but not before he raised the alarm. That was all right, though. That was the plan.

Within a few minutes they were within a hundred yards of Nurmengard, and the guards - the Hírnökei - were pouring out. The four squads separated, moving to assigned places. Gimel Group and Daleth Group (Hig's own) engaged. They swooped in and out, diving as if they were Seekers, and dodged curses. The Americans concentrated on their defenses, working together to support shields. As was usual, each of them had paired off with an attacker in that odd instinctive way that happened during a battle, and the matches appeared to be even ones for the most part. Stunners whipped up and down, and a few found their marks. When the Americans were able, they cast Deprimo on the ground around their attackers, trying to disrupt footing and generate mayhem, and several of the witches in Gimel also began emptying out mokeskin pouches full of Bluebell Flames. The Hírnökei spent some time in attacking with Fumos and other gaseous effects, perhaps not realizing their attackers had Bubblehead Charms on or perhaps hoping to disrupt their vision, before settling down to more traditional stunners. They had the red handprint insignia of the Veres Kezek on their robes, so perhaps they were too used to murdering Muggles: the "Red Hands" had been last deployed to Poland, as far as Hig knew, and they had left that area a bloody ruin.

Meanwhile, Aleph and Beth went to the side of Nurmengard that rose straight from the cliff below. Hig saw them swoop away from the corner of his eye as he swerved his broom to avoid a curse. No defenders could come out on that side to try to curse them, and there were no windows. As long as they kept very low and close to the wall, they'd be almost completely obscured. Nurmengard was magnificent and terrifying, but it was not originally designed to be a military base, and its design had shortcomings. Aleph and Beth were trying to take advantage of that to breach the fortress walls, as though they intended to storm the fortress by that route.

Fifteen minutes later, which seemed like an eternity of swerving and casting and screaming, Aleph and Beth Groups both flew back into sight, soaring up from below the cliff's edge to catch the defenders by surprise. They took down three or four, although that still left at least twenty.

This was supposed to be the signal for Gimel to disengage, but they'd already lost five of their number. Gimel's leader, Momo, shot out red sparks as he flew. He corkscrewed to avoid a cascade of curses from the duo of Hírnökei that he had been fighting, and the red sparks pinwheeled out behind him, flittering brightly. It was the signal for Daleth to take Gimel's place. Hig immediately broke off the fight, along with the seven remaining members of Daleth Group. From wherever they were on the battlefield, they flew to Nurmengard's roof.

There were still two guards there, firing at the attackers; Grindelwald was cautious. Hig and several others on Daleth flew up the wall, holding tight to its side. They were to the top and over the edge before the guards could react. One brandished his wand and shouted, "Állj!" Hig thought that meant "stop." He did not oblige.

It wasn't a pretty fight - at least one of the guards was unusually skilled, firing curses with remarkable rapidity, while the other guard was actually willing to cast the Killing Curse. Even in war, that was unusual, and despite outnumbering the guards four to one, Hig lost another of his soldiers before it was done.

Hig assessed Daleth Group quickly. Seven total, including himself. Almost all Westphalians, including Tineagar, Sammy Shohet, and three others. One Argentine had also made it to this point: a skinny and handsome bald man with a toothbrush mustache. Hig couldn't remember his name - the chaos had cleared it right out of his head. Didn't matter.

They were inside in moments. Dumbledore had been able to tell them about much of the layout - who knew how he'd found out - and so they knew that it was only a short flight of stairs down to a large and defensible storage room. There was a door, but it was unenchanted, and so Hig's group blew it apart and stormed in. There was no one else there, although surely that would soon change. The outside war and the diversionary attacks at the base of the fortress might have given them some breathing room to breach, but there was a limit to how effective that could be. It was the best advantage that highly mobile attackers could wield against stationary defenders, but the Hírnökei were here in force: perhaps the whole of the Veres Kezek and maybe another squad like the Záh Kardja, besides.

Hig, the Argentinian, and Shohet took up guarding position at the other door, reinforcing it and putting up hasty wards. Tineagar and the other four knelt and touched their wands to the fitted stone underfoot. They put their free hands on their neighbors' shoulders, so that the five of them were interlocked in a pentagon. They began casting.

Nurmengard was harnessed to a ley line, and that power fairly thrummed through the building. It was a mighty work, enacted by one of the most powerful wizards in the world and his ablest lieutenants, but it was also limited. Almost all of the ley energy went into the enchantments that prevented time-turning, apparating, and any transfiguration of the fortress walls. It was a seat of power and a prison… but it was no Wizengamot or Qufu. It had weaknesses.

There was shouting from the other side of the door in angry Hungarian. "Dögölj meg! Rothadjanak ki az anyád szemei!" Hig didn't understand much of it… definitely ordering him to die like an animal, and something about his mother. Curses smashed into the door, along with disenchantments. The wood glowed red in spots, and blackened in others, but Shohet countered with a Flame-Freezing Charm, and Hig put up another Colloportus. They needed to hold for at least a few minutes, but it was just going to get harder with every second.

"Guests are knocking!" Hig shouted at the quintet kneeling in the room behind him, as he froze the door hinges in place with Immobulus to stop a Hírnöke from blasting them free. There was no reply, and he probably shouldn't have said anything. If they could hear him, they could hear the curses, anyway.

"A nagyobb jó érdekében!" came the cry from the other side of the door. Their slogan, which every combatant knew by now: "for the greater good."

There was silence from the other side of the door, so Hig and Shohet simultaneously sealed off any cracks above, below, or through the door with an immediate and hastily conjured wall of iron. If your opponent was silent, then they were probably transfiguring something nasty that would drown you in your own blood with noxious gas.

They never found out if they'd been right, or if the Hírnökei were just deciding what to try next, because Tineagar and the other four suddenly succeeded in charming the floor beneath them. One moment, the seven members of Daleth Group were trying to guard a door, and the next… well, it was as though the floor dropped right out from under them without actually moving. The Butterball Charm was weak, but it was enough so that all seven of them and all of the storage lockers in the room slipped right through a floor that was suddenly too liquid to support them. There was a tremendous crash and painful thump as everything and everyone in the room dropped down through seven feet of fitted stone right into the room below.

This was their objective. A direct fight to bring them to this point would have taken hours and gone through three defensive chokepoints, if they could have done it at all. Dumbledore had said that a quick swim would be easier, and he had been right. He had also been right about what was in the room: seven orange crystal balls, spangled with glowing red stars. Satomi's Dogs, spoken of in legend and acquired by Grindelwald at a terrible cost.

Dumbledore was wrong about one thing, though. He'd said that Grindelwald would trust no one with access to this room, but there were three people waiting there.

One of the defending Hírnökei was crushed by a storage locker, hammered into the stone wetly, but the others barely even paused in their surprise. Instinct took over, and the defenders - Záh Kardja, as Hig had thought - attacked. They got off three curses in a matter of moments, while Hig was still struggling to find his wand in a slurry of liquid stone.

"Stupefy! Stupefy!"

"Avada Kedavra!"

Shohet fell, stunned and then murdered in quick succession. The Argentinian fell stunned. Hig found his wand, as did another member of Daleth, but it was still too slow.

"Stupefy!"

"Stupefy! Stupefy!"

The Latinate curses had the raw accent of Hungarian, but they were no less effective. Attackers dropped stiffly to the ground. By his count, only Hig was left. Still, only one person was needed to smash these damn crystal balls. He raised his wand and successfully cursed one of the two defenders, "Stupefy!", and then turned his wand to cast again in quick succession.

Not quick enough. The other Hírnöke hit him with an Immobulus in the same instant, and Hig felt his body stiffen. He leaned to the side, caught in an awkward position with one arm thrust forward, and felt himself tilt until he came to a rest against the wall, still upright. The Hírnöke must be a Legilimens, and want quick answers, Hig thought, cursing inwardly. He was not a Occlumens, and couldn't close his eyes while frozen.

The Hírnöke stalked over to him. She was a nasty-looking woman. Not that Hig thought he was any prize, but this witch had long curving scars all across her face. They looked like punishment, but she had the sword emblem of the Záh Kardja: they might be a point of pride.

"Véget vetnénk minden szenvedésnek. Megállítanátok minket? Bolondok," she spat at him through cleft lips. He had not the faintest idea what that meant, and he couldn't have answered if he'd wanted to. His heart sank. If Satomi's Dogs remained intact, then everything was lost.

"Expelliarmus!" called a voice Hig recognized as Tineagar's.

He'd miscounted.

The Hírnöke's wand was ripped from her fingers and soared over to Tineagar, who was still rising to her feet. The American snapped it neatly out of the air, and darted her wand in Hig's direction just long enough to Innervate him. Hig went sprawling against the wall, choking on a magically-sustained breath.

"Hig, you okay?" Tineagar called, leveling her wand back on the Záh Kardja.

"Yes," he gasped. "Don't wait, just do it now!" Every second they delayed was another second that Grindelwald was channeling power through these crystals. Hig didn't understand how it worked - he suspected that no one but Dumbledore and Grindelwald could have even hazarded a guess - but they were some vital part to Grindelwald's invincible strength. This was April 30th, and every part of the plan had to go correctly. It was a masterpiece of strategy and tactics, and Hig had been left in awe when Momo and Dumbledore had devised it, but it would all fail unless they destroyed Satomi's Dogs. No time for discussion.

"Reducto!" cast Tineagar, leveling her wand at one of the Dogs. It exploded into pinkish glass dust as the blue bolt struck it, destroyed in a moment. Tineagar paused to gather her strength into her tall and thin body, then moved from one Dog to the next, destroying each of the seven in turn, as quickly as she could.

Above them, Hig heard an explosion. But it didn't matter that the rest of the attackers were soon to be storming down upon them, since Tineagar had just turned and obliterated the last of the crystal balls. Hig readied himself, even as the Hírnöke snarled something completely foreign, heavy with bitterness. "Láttuk a jóslatokat és tudjuk, hogy még győzni fogunk. Lesz egy ember akit a villám megjelölt és ő kioltja majd a csillagokat."

Tineagar cut off any more chatter from the Hungarian with a curt stunner, then turned to Hig. "We did it."

"Yes. But it will, I think, be the last thing we do." Hig moved to a corner of the room. They'd have to drop down to get him, and he'd get a clear shot at the first one at least. He wished they had the time and strength to revive their frozen friends, but that would just leave them unable to defend themselves when the attack came.

As she mimicked him and moved to a different corner, Tineagar said, "It was worth it." She glanced at the stunned enemies. "I can't abide this nonsense about the ends justifying the means… about how they want to fix everything, so all the murder and madness is worth it." Tineagar raised her wand, and set her features grimly. "I don't care what kind of good you think you're going to do, and I don't care what kind of person you think you are. It's your actions that matter, not your goals. To the pit with tyrants and all their people."

Her kind of irreducible skepticism had its uses. He shouldn't have been so hasty to judge her. Not that it mattered, now.

"Hello? Reg? Sammy?"

Hig blinked. He called up, surprised, "Momo?"

"Yes!" called his ally. "Get up here - we can't block the corridor much longer! We need to form a line of defense!"

But before he'd even finished speaking, Hig and Tineagar were beginning to Innervate the fallen (except for poor Shohet) as quickly as they could manage. That wasn't very quickly at all, given their exhaustion, but it was fast enough that six witches and wizards were able to join their comrades before the Hírnökei could break through to them.

The Americans' blood was up, and they roared their anger when the Hírnökei came - the remains of Veres Kezek and Záh Kardja. The Hírnökei shouted their own fanatical screams in return. And there was war. Bloody and bitter war, fought in the halls of Nurmengard and atop its battlement. Many died that day, and others would long bear the curse scars for years to come.

You probably know the rest of the story - or at least, you know the romantic parts about Dumbledore and Grindelwald, and how ambition soured into madness, and love curdled after a single tragic accident. Certainly, you know about the great duel between the two. It is said to be the greatest duel ever yet fought, justly citing the long hours over which it ceaselessly raged, the unstoppable force of Dumbledore's skill, and the immovable object of Grindelwald's defenses.

Grindelwald held the Elder Wand, and was sustained by Satomi's Dogs, and guarded by the Iron Halo. While it is known that he stole the Elder Wand from Mykew Gregorovitch, it is not yet known how he came by his other great devices. But they were all powerful, and they preserved him against all ills, like an unbreachable barrier a hundred metres high.

There are twenty-eight books about Grindelwald's War, seven books about the rivalry and lives of Dumbledore and Grindelwald, and three books just about that single duel. And yet it is certain that he would never have fallen, Dumbledore notwithstanding - all else notwithstanding - had the Americans not succeeded in breaching Nurmengard and destroying Satomi's Dogs.

Reg Hig learned something about Limpel Tineagar that day. He learned about her steel, and he learned her value. And Hig took her words about the "greater good" to heart, too. He would remember them.

Chapter 15: Pip's Day Out

GRANGER ON AMERICAN TOUR: 'A LOVELY HOLIDAY IN THE STATES'

- Daily Prophet headline for March 14th, 1999

STATES IN TREATY TALKS

- Daily Prophet headline for March 16th, 1999

LONDON EUPHORIC RING EXPOSED

- Daily Prophet headline for March 17th, 1999

LINNAEAN LUNACY: LOVEGOOD ACCUSED OF SMUGGLING 4X BEASTS

- Daily Prophet headline for March 20th, 1999

TREATY FAILS IN USA: RISING SUPPORT FOR 'HONOURABLE'

- Daily Prophet headline for March 30th, 1999

AFRICAN SWEEP: NIGERIA, FREE STATES IN TREATY

- Daily Prophet headline for April 1st, 1999

BULSTRODE ARRESTED IN CONNECTION WITH DIAGON BOMBING

- Daily Prophet headline for April 2nd, 1999

BULSTRODE GOES BEFORE WIZENGAMOT: CARROW: 'SHALLOW POLITICAL PLOY'

- Daily Prophet headline for April 3rd, 1999

BULSTRODE RELEASED: N'GOMA: 'KNOWS NOTHING ABOUT ANYTHING.'

- Daily Prophet headline for April 4th, 1999

TOWER TO OPEN FOR SQUIBS

- Daily Prophet headline for April 5th, 1999

TREATY SURPRISE: WESTPHALIA REOPENS ISSUE WITH NEW DEMANDS

- Daily Prophet headline for April 5th, 1999

≡≡≡Ω≡≡≡

April 7th, 1999

5:30 a.m.

Outskirts of Curd, Tipperary, Ireland

Pip kept up a quick step as he walked down the winding path that led to Curd. He tried to look smart, with his head high and shoulders back. He was a representative of the Government of magical Britain and of the Tower, and he had to look the part. Considering how busy things were going to be back at the Tower, he should thank his lucky stars to be out on delivery duty, anyway.

He'd been here before, on similar errands. The cobblestone path was not very well-maintained, since it was only used by the relatively few wizards and witches who visited the city. You weren't allowed to Apparate or fly directly into Curd; you had to go to a "welcome platform" (a cleared dirt area a half-mile away from the city) and then walk down the "welcome path" (on which rough cobblestones you might stub your toe) through the "welcome gate" (which crawled with wards and precautions). Considering the names of everything, he thought sourly, it wasn't very ruddy welcoming at all.

There was a chill in the air at this early hour. It felt pleasant on Pip's face, since it didn't touch the rest of him thanks to a Warming Charm. It reminded him of something he could remember his dad liked to say, quoting from a book and tugging on his beard with solemnity: "There is no quality in this world that is not what it is merely by contrast." Pip felt vaguely guilty at the thought. He'd never been much for reading, and particularly not Muggle books. He really should try to read something this month - a real book, not just The Adventures of Martin Miggs, the Mad Muggle. Wasn't there a new Lockhart out? He'd liked the vampire one.

Curd lay before him - the town of towers. Low sandstone buildings with sloping walls were all topped with at least one conical tower. None of the towers were very high. Pip supposed that was probably because the gobbies couldn't build Floo networks, and it would be a bother to go up and down a lot of stairs. Maybe that would change, soon.

Pip sighed as he marched down the path. The town looked like it had been made out of a child's toy blocks.

A few minutes along, he was finally nearing the outskirts. He passed a pair of guards sitting in a small pavilion next to the welcome gate, and nodded to them with great dignity as he passed through. The two goblins were armored in silver plate: cuirass, cuisses, and vambraces. They didn't wear any helmets, so he could see them grin horribly at him. Their short spears sat on a rack nearby, but they didn't even bother to get up. Maybe they recognized him - Pip had a bit of trouble telling goblins apart (except for Podrut in Material Methods, who had a distinctive notch in his right ear), but the goblins never seemed to have the same problem with humans.

Wait, should he have said something to them? He'd just nodded to them and hadn't said anything. They hadn't looked bothered, though. Just bored. But he didn't want them to think he was rude, or that the Tower was rude, or anything. J.C. had said that goblins valued truth more than anything, and that they were suspicious of politeness, but Pip thought that was probably just something they wanted everyone to think. It probably made people trust Gringott's more. Although J.C. did seem like she would know, as a senior auror - she was all sharp edges and grimness. Plus he'd heard that she had some gobbie blood. But that might just be one of the rumors probies passed around during training, on account of her wide mouth and the largish ears that poked out of her curly black hair, and because she was so skinny. It could be true, but there were rumors like that about everyone who was even a little different. Tall people had giantish ancestry, pretty people had veela ancestry, people with bad teeth had mermish ancestry… Silly, really. When he'd been stationed in Nurmengard, there had been a German auror with really red hair, and he'd heard someone whisper with complete seriousness that she had phoenix ancestry, which didn't even make any sense. That would have meant that someone had been with a phoenix at some point, and then… what, hatched a baby with it? It was as silly and weird as when people said that the Goddess had unicorn ancestry.

Oh, Merlin. He'd forgotten about the guards. Well, he'd gone way too far to turn back and say anything now.

Pip stepped off the welcome path onto the large flagstones of Curd's streets. An extremely obese goblin man wheeling a little cart squinted at him suspiciously, but said nothing. Not a friendly lot, here.

Okay, so let's see… he needed to go down this street, and then left at the bronze statue of the angry goblin with his fist raised (Crad the Callow, Pip thought it was), then another left at the town market, and then straight on to the Burgod Bur. That was where they put up notices and delivered regulations, and Pip had a stack of them.

Goblin names were a nightmare, really. He didn't know how they kept it sorted out. Curd's government was in the Burgod Bur, while Ackle's was in the Urgod Ur, and if you confused those they thought it was really funny even though they sounded almost identical to humans. And they kept using the same names with no surname: the Chief Goldsmith of Gringotts right now was Haddad, not to be confused with Haddad the Silent or Haddad the Hallowed from goblin history (wait, was it Hodrod the Hallowed?). And all the buildings were called things like Poddle Pol, Sugworn Sug, Togrigworn Tog, and whatnot. Impossible to keep them straight! He knew that the way place-name syllables were repeated meant something about the purpose of the building, but he'd never been much for Gobbledegook. It all just sounded silly to him, instead… like the babbling of a baby.

Pip followed the street, glancing around as he walked. Part of the reason they did this by hand, instead of by owl, was that it gave them a chance to take a look at things. Tourism in Curd or Ackle was discouraged, and so the only way to keep tabs on the goblins was with regular official visits. Pip knew that they'd been a lot more intrusive in the past, with wizarding inspectors and regulators and so on, always barging in on the gobbies and making sure everything was on the up-and-up. That made sense to him, since every witch and wizard knew how violent they could be. But that had all been scaled back over the past few years - partly as part of the new cooperative arrangements that the Ministry had made (putting the Tribunes in the Wizengamot), and partly because so many government employees had been sacked.

All the layoffs had brought down Minister for Magic Junius Simplewort Smith (although thankfully not Senior Undersecretary Weasley, who Pip thought was a good bloke), but no one was hired back, even under new Minister for Magic Carmel N'goma. Even if the Ministry wanted to start poking their noses into goblin business all the time, like they used to do, they probably wouldn't have the staff. The sacked inspectors and bureaucrats had all been offered training and loans to start new businesses, and most everyone had moved on with their lives (well, except for those who had started supporting the Malfoys).

The statue of Crad the Callow was in sight, and Pip walked past it and turned left. He wasn't sure why ol' Crad had a statue - the inscription was in Gobbledegook - but he assumed it was probably because of some rebellion or another. Professor Binns had droned on for hours about the rebellions, when Pip was in school.

Pip turned left again once he reached the market, which was almost deserted at this hour. The handful of vendors pulling canvas covers off of their carts and tables paid him no mind except for an occasional glare. Honestly, Pip couldn't help but think gobbies were an ungrateful lot. Goblins controlled a third of the money in the entire country through Gringotts (which bank they'd taken from wizards only a century and a half ago), and he knew they used that power all the time to help themselves out. Further, the Wand Ban had been repealed, and now they were allowed to legally buy and use wands. They'd even been given a seat on the Wizengamot with that Suffrage Decree, six years ago! You'd think they'd show a little gratitude towards wizards and witches, these days, considering what had been done for them.

The Burgod Bur wasn't very impressive… just another sandstone building with slotted windows and a tower. There was Gobbledegook carved in above the door, and a pair of guards, but it was otherwise indistinguishable from most other Curdish buildings. It's odd… Gringotts was a beautiful building of white marble, with Greek columns and bronze doors and glittering lamps. But Curd and Ackle were both very plain places. Pip did have to admit that he'd seen very little of the two goblin settlements, but even with his limited perspective, there was a clear disjunction between them and the bank.

Pip gave the armored guards a nod as he walked in. These were more attentive, but they just nodded their helmeted heads in return. They were each armed with fancy golden partisans which probably had long names and thousand-year-histories, and which probably cost ten times as much as Pip's house.

A goblin in a dapper black suit stood just inside the Burgod Bur, and stepped forward as Pip approached. Pip thought he recognized the goblin, but it was hard to be sure... He hesitated slightly, then risked a greeting: "Hullo, Nagrod."

The goblin smiled toothily and bowed slightly. "Auror Pirrip. What a surprise to see you!" Almost certainly a lie - Nagrod was very good at his job. Pip wasn't entirely sure what that job actually was, but it was bloody well clear at this point that some large part of it involved knowing the name, purpose, history, and shoe size of every visitor to Curd.

"Well, they need someone to plod on out with these things," Pip said. He unbuckled the slicebox at his belt and reached inside, pulling out a sheaf of parchment. "A new decree from the Wizengamot and a new rejuvenation policy from the Tower."

"Ah, the two pillars of your society, handing down rules to us," Nagrod said, managing to sound completely neutral. "May I ask?"

Pip handed the sheaf over to the goblin. "The new decree is not very interesting. Guess that's both bad news and good news. It's just about extending the Floo Network."

Until recently, the Government had always declined to put the settlements of any Beings on the network, but they'd decided to reverse that policy and offer the services of the Floo Network Authority to anyone who requested it, Beings included. Here in Curd, that meant they could connect with places like Dublin or Helga's Roost, if they so desired. That might make travel to England somewhat easier, since they could Floo to Dublin and then buy a portkey.

"Must have been quite the stir in Ackle over this, though," Nagrod said, taking the parchments. "Will the heirs of Togrod Teulu be putting themselves one fireplace away from the Ministry, I wonder?"

Pip didn't venture a comment on that, since that sounded like gobbie politics. He buckled the slicebox back on his belt, instead, fixing the thin wooden box back in place. It had been his suggestion to use them for carrying parchment. Well, not so much his deliberate suggestion… he'd just assumed that was their purpose, and so he'd asked for one at the DMLE when they gave him this assignment, yesterday. Chief Auror Diggory hadn't known what he was talking about, but Pip had gone back to the Tower and asked around, and Mr. Potter himself had been delighted by the idea. He'd called them an unintentional byproduct of testing, and said that they had loads of the useless things, and that Pip was a genius. Pip had told his mother about it, and she'd baked him a Whirlibird Cake to celebrate.

Nagrod glanced over the first few sheets, before looking back up. The goblin's long nose was crooked at the arch, and looked more like a hawk's beak than a nose. He blinked owlishly for a moment, then asked Pip, "And what news from the Tower?"

"Even less exciting for you, I'm afraid. They're opening up rejuvenation to Muggles. Direct relatives and Squibs and all that." Pip shrugged.

This would be big news in London, Godric's Hollow, and other human settlements… but less so for Beings, who were already enjoying the benefits of rejuvenation and Safety Poles. Madame Bones had put precautions in place to make sure everything went in an orderly fashion; there were going to be special groups of aurors stationed at the Poles, in addition to the normal pairs of clinic workers who manned those stations, to make sure that the Tower didn't get mobbed as it first opened its doors to Muggles. It was still only a small fraction of Muggles, but there was always a rush whenever any new group was allowed to rejuvenate. When British merfolk signed on to the Treaty for Health and Life in late 1997, Pip had heard that they were shipping in water tanks of old and sick and dying half-people from the Black Lake and Loch Lomond for a solid two days. Before his time in the Tower, of course, but the other aurors talked about it (mostly because of the smell).

"This will be a busy day for you, then," Nagrod said. He lowered the sheaf of papers, after looking carefully for any surprises. "What is a 'direct relative,' though? Mother, brother, uncle, grandfather, cousin, brother-in-law, second cousin twice removed… you will be having many arguments about this."

"Not me… at least, not today," Pip said, brightly. "I'm out on delivery, all day. Here, Dublin, and Helga's Roost, then over to Godric's Hollow and Ackle and down to Wales and all over London." His list of destinations was a long one… these decrees went out to every sizeable community in Britain. "And anyway, they spell out who's eligible, but they're usually really soft about that kind of thing. Anyone who's seriously hurt… they whisk them right in, as fast as they can."

"Really..? How interesting… say, where else are you heading, today?" Nagrod said, thoughtfully. Pip didn't like where this was going, and he'd spent enough time here. He still had that bloody long walk back to the "welcome platform." And honestly, what sort of question was that? Was Nagrod trying to chat him up?

Pip briefly considered what that would be like, and then cleared his throat loudly. "Yes, well, I better be going. You'll put those up, will you?" he said, uncomfortably.

"It would be my pleasure, Auror Pip," Nagrod said, smiling widely. Sharp little teeth shone whitely from behind thick little lips.

Pip nodded firmly and - he hoped - professionally, and got out of there. Today was going to be a long day, full of cryptic conversations, he could tell already.

≡≡≡Ω≡≡≡

April 7th, 1999

3:01 p.m.

Diagon Alley, London, England

"Three Galleons, young man. Final offer. That's a great deal of money for just a few minutes of discomfort," said Jerina. "You won't even feel it… it'll be numb as a stone. Then a very quick turn of the knife, and it'll be done in moments. Two spells later, you'll be walking out of here just as you came in, only with quite a bit more coin. Likho will be right here… she'll watch and make sure it's done right. And this knife is as sharp as a razor."

"No, thank you, ma'am," Pip said, as pleasantly and courteously as possible under the circumstances. One did not trifle with a hag, even a Nutcombe hag. Even if you were an auror and you were there on official business. No trifling. "I apologize, but I think it would make me uncomfortable, and I must decline."

"It's a waste, is all," said Jerina, sadly. "Young fellow like you, athletic type… good calves. Firm and lean. Four Galleons."

"Jerina," said Likho, warningly. The elder hag stood nearby, arms crossed. Stout almost to the point of obesity, with a spine that twisted into a hump and greyish skin, Likho was firm with her flock. Two long yellow teeth jutted up past her stern lips.

Jerina grimaced, scrunching up her wart-covered face in suffering.

Pip had seen a play once about an Italian named Ugolino. The leading actor had torn at his clothes and howled at the sky and beat the ground with his fists. He had wept until his eyes looked raw and his mouth was a round "O" of unhappiness. And yet there was far more pain in Jerina's expression right at this moment, twisted in agony and need, as she begged to be allowed to eat his flesh.

He almost agreed, just to give her some relief.

"Jerina…" Likho repeated, and the younger hag turned away, slamming her fists down against her legs. Jerina stalked away, out of the parlor and out of sight. Pip didn't permit himself a sigh or a change in posture, but kept a pleasant smile stiffly pasted on his mouth. His cheeks hurt from maintaining it.

Likho watched Jerina go, then turned to Pip. "I apologize, Auror Pirrip. She is young, and it is difficult."

"I understand, ma'am, and accept your apology," he said. Did that sound false? Damn it, Pip… Be sincere be sincere be sincere be sincere… "I hope that Miss Jerina soon feels better."

Likho nodded absently, turning to look back at where Jerina had gone. The older hag's eyes were a tawny and beautiful gold, quite out of keeping with the rest of her physical hideousness. Pip had read that a hag's eyes were always blood-red - like Jerina's - but he supposed that the effect must be a result of Likho's abstinence from human meat. She was famously self-controlled, which was why she led the Nutcombe Society.

"Tell me, Auror Pirrip, about the Tower," Likho said to him. "Tell me about the man. I've met him, twice, but only on formal occasions. What sort of man is he?"

Pip thought carefully - very carefully - for a moment, then said, "Well, ma'am, he's very strange… very much in his own head. He makes jokes that no one understands, like calling aurors 'red shirts.' And I think he's a little lonely. But maybe that's like most people in power." He considered for another long moment. He didn't want to give a bad impression of Mr. Potter. But neither was he going to lie or dissemble. Not here. No trifling. "I think probably the most important thing about him is that he doesn't want anyone to get hurt."

Likho nodded, and Pip got the impression that she was no longer paying attention. Hags could see things that no one else could see. It wasn't the future, exactly… They just seemed to reach bizarre and inexplicable conclusions than everyone else - one famous hag had insisted that she was meant to be married to a teenage boy that she'd just met. That had made headlines for weeks.

Honoria Nutcombe herself could only ever say that they could "see all the things that were real." Pip wasn't enough of a scholar to know what that meant, so he only abided by Madame Bones' advice to the Shichinin, which he'd overheard last year: "When dealing with a hag, gentlemen, be scrupulously polite and expeditiously brief."

These hags, at least, were trying to be civilized. He didn't know what they ate, when they couldn't get someone to agree to sell them a bit of themselves, but it seemed quite difficult for them. Maybe they didn't really have to eat at all. Pip had no interest in loitering about to find out.

After a bit, Likho spoke up again, asking, "And does he know the cause of the narrowing?"

Pip had not the smallest idea what that might mean, and so he erred on the side of caution. "I don't know, ma'am."

"Very well. Thank you, then, Auror Pirrip. Good afternoon."

All day like this, Pip thought glumly, as he bowed slightly and left the Nutcombe Society. His smile was still plastered on his face. He'd already been to Curd, Dublin, Helga's Roost, and Godric's Hollow, and at every stop there was someone asking him things that were entirely unanswerable about recent events or the Tower or rejuvenation, asking about things that their seers or oneiromancers or neladoracht had told them.

Maybe there was a reason Diggory kept sending him on these assignments.

≡≡≡Ω≡≡≡

April 7th, 1999

3:04 p.m.

Salor Sprig, The Forbidden Forest, Scotland

"No, sir, I don't know what the meaning of 'is,' is," Pip said, patiently. "Just the usual meaning, I suppose."

Roonwit rumbled deep in his chest and struck the dirt with an idle hoof. "What is usual to me may not be usual to you, human. The subordination of the rigor of definition to the glib gesturing towards 'usual' - by which you mean, 'custom;' the humbling of writing beneath a speech dreaming its plenitude; such are the gestures required by an onto-theology determining the archaeological and eschatological meaning of being as presence, as parousia, as life without difference: another name for death, historical metonymy where God's name holds death in check. That is why, if this movement begins its era in the form of Platonism, it ends in infinitist metaphysics. If we follow your feeble logic where it will, there is no end to our questioning - we'll never really communicate, since we'll never know what a word truly means." He gestured with an immense spear at the sky, as though waving the needle point at the futility of language.

"Roonwit, you are speaking in deliberately difficult language, and that is why you are not really communicating," said Cloudbirth, who was standing nearby. He clopped over, flanks shining in the sun overhead. "Just speak clearly, and trust that you will make your point. Don't try to hide in jargon like the Fontainebleau."

Pip nodded gratefully at Cloudbirth, but the centaur wasn't done. Cloudbirth went on, and his dangerous, flashing eye cut off Pip before he could speak, "The same principle holds, you know, for more everyday matters. Even in social life, you will never make a good impression on other people until you stop thinking about what sort of impression you are making. Even in literature and art, no man who bothers about originality will ever be original whereas if you simply try to tell the truth you will, nine times out of ten, become original without ever having noticed it. The principle runs through all life from top to bottom: Give up yourself, and you will find your real self."

"Is there anyone else I can speak to, sir?" Pip asked, politely.

"Elder Glenstorm!" called Roonwit, gesturing across the clearing at a centaur who was standing next to one of the rough bark shacks that were the only buildings at the Salor Sprig. The named centaur looked up from his book, startled, and put it carefully on a shelf within one of the shacks, and trotted over. He took a wide berth around the center of the grassy clearing, where the sacred sapling grew.

"Afternoon," Glenstorm said. He was a blue roan, with broad sides of a dusty grey. A longbow was slung across his human torso, and a quiver of arrows swung along his equine shoulder, kept from abrading with an oilcloth. "Are you two foals harassing this young human?"

"Elder Glenstorm has a smooth mouth, and much experience speaking with humans," said Cloudbirth, kindly. "We learn to think first, and it is only with time that we develop concision."

"Thank y-" began Pip, but Cloudbirth wasn't finished.

"We do our best, of course," continued Cloudbirth, "but some of the humans from your Ministry have given very unbalanced accounts of our aim, as though the wine which is the reward of all our labors was the anguish and bewilderment of a human. We merely follow a general rule: in all activities of mind which favor our cause of wisdom, encourage oneself to be un-selfconscious and to concentrate on that object, but in all other activities bend the mind back on itself and fix the attention inward. It is the best way to restrain our native temperaments."

"Enough, enough," murmured Glenstorm. Cloudbirth frowned and thumped the ground. The elder centaur turned to Pip. "It is unwise to come to the Salor Sprig without good cause, auror. Matters between our peoples have much improved, of late, but cross half a distance and half yet remains."

Oh, Merlin.

"I would like to post these two announcements. One is from the Ministry, and one is from the Tower," Pip said, remaining as calm as he was able. "I don't think either of them affect your people very much."

"We will be the judge of that," said Glenstorm, curtly. At least he was brief. Pip handed the sheaf of parchment up to the elder centaur, happy to be rid of his charge and eager to be gone.

"Yes, well," Pip said, backing up, "Please do." One never really recognized just how ruddy big a horse-man could be until you were standing uncomfortably in the middle of three of them.

"More to do with wizard kin than the people," Glenstorm said to Roonwit, after scanning the sheaf of parchment. "The auror is quite right. I will speak to the other elders about this, but I see nothing to intrude upon us, here. We will be able to keep our hands clean. Firenze is wrong, again."

Roonwit hefted his spear in one hand and transferred it to the other, as if impatient with it. Pip wasn't exactly sure if Roonwit was a posted guard here, or just carrying the spear for protection or a ceremony or… some other unknowable mysterious centaur purpose. They were proper weird. They were an exceedingly private and outrageously proud people, only sending out rare emissaries to wizardkind when they felt forced to do so. Not a single one had consented to be rejuvenated or even healed by the Tower, despite the Salor Sprig's Safety Pole.

Pip's Head of House back in school, Severus Snape, had once spoken of centaurs in the common room, when a plot was being hatched to get rid of Professor Trelawney (who was widely believed to favor Gryffindor students). She was high-strung, and three enterprising Slytherins had plotted to start leaving her notes in her own handwriting (as best they could manage it) informing her that she'd been Obliviated, and telling her about all sorts of terrible things that she'd witnessed important people doing. Snape had discovered the plot, and while he approved of this plan in terms of conception and cleverness (not that he could ever have actually countenanced such actions against a fellow professor) he had been merciless in mocking their next step: to invite a centaur to teach in Trelawney's place, once she'd been stuffed into St. Mungo's. Pip was unclear on the purpose of that replacement, but he thought it had been rooted in a basic assumption that the centaur would fail so badly they'd just eliminate Divination altogether.

Snape had said that centaurs were monstrously jealous of their privacy: they spent their lives in pursuit of philosophy, divination, and medicine - three practices that inherently involved interacting with strangers - and yet still worked tirelessly to isolate themselves from the unwashed masses. Any centaur who deigned to accept a teaching assignment at Hogwarts would be beaten and cast out from his people. "No member of that race," Snape had sneered, "would pay a permanent price for a temporary position. They are self-involved, not outright imbecilic."

Pip sometimes thought that the Sorting Hat had been wrong, putting him in Slytherin.

Roonwit spoke again, gruffly. "My apologies to you, auror, if I was too obscure. The pursuit of meaning is an important one, but I have been perhaps too-long devoted to the contemplation of signifier and signified. It is a matter of great importance to me… it is immortality."

"Metaphorically, you mean," replied Cloudbirth. "Such a conceit can't give any real guidance to action… What is the good of telling the ships how to steer so as to avoid collisions if, in fact, they are such crazy old tubs that they cannot be steered at all?"

"Not at all! True immortality… and it is inherent in every sign!" said Roonwit. "Every sign, linguistic or nonlinguistic, spoken or written, as a small or large unity, can be cited, put between quotation marks; thereby it can break with every given context, and engender infinitely new contexts in an absolutely nonsaturable fashion. This does not suppose that the mark is valid outside its context, but on the contrary that there are only contexts without any center of absolute anchoring. This citationality, duplication, or duplicity, this iterability of the mark is not an accident or anomaly, but is that normal or abnormal without which a mark could no longer even have a so-called 'normal' functioning. What would a mark be that one could not cite? And whose origin could not be lost on the way? It would be an immortal sign, alive because an end cannot approach that which does not have a beginning."

Pip must have been revealing too much on his face - or maybe Glenstorm really was just more thoughtful than the other centaurs - because the elder centaur waved him on, signaling that he could leave.

He was starting to understand why he had the full sweep of messenger duty today, and not a more experienced auror. The goblins were strange, but fine. He'd be happy to keep going back to Curd and Ackle, like he had before. Even the Nutcombe Society was only unnerving and dangerous.

But this…

Whoever regularly brought messages to the Salor Sprig deserved a promotion and a crate of firewhiskey.

≡≡≡Ω≡≡≡

April 7th, 1999

7:28 p.m.

The Receiving Room, Hogwarts, Scotland

When Pip got back to the Tower after his very long day (fourteen different places!), people were arriving in the Receiving Room at the rate of seven or eight people a minute, and all the receiving aurors looked ragged. The foreigners looked worst of all - Pip supposed that they had fewer people on their team to relieve them, but were still expected to put in their fair share.

The elderly and injured and diseased appeared, spinning in from a sideways that was always orthogonal to the viewer, and coming to a rest softly. Usually, they still glowed a faint red from the stunning effect of the trip. As they arrived, one of the aurors would examine them for a second, and then a pair would get to work scanning and dispelling. After years of practice - including other mad days like today - most of the sizeable contingent of receiving aurors were old hands at the work, and patients were either wheeled in through the golden entrance to the Tower or moved into an adjacent room for other assistance or questioning.

The on-site workers at the Safety Poles usually did a decent job of triage, and kept back those who didn't actually need the Tower's assistance, but those facilities - some of which were growing to be full-fledged hospitals to rival St. Mungo's, squatting protectively around their individual Safety Poles - weren't perfect. And almost a third of all visitors traveled via Safety Stick instead, directly from their homes or work. Some of them were only panicking, some of them only needed first aid, and many had just made a mistake with the Safety Stick. A surprising number of children thought "running safety" was just a lark.

On a day like today, with Muggles and Squibs arriving… well, who knew how many things had gone wrong today? Pip knew that the Obliviator Squad had been expanded and was scheduled to work around the clock for the next two weeks, until they'd worked out all the kinks in the system. Even everyone in the Magical Law Enforcement Patrol had been scheduled for extra shifts, filling in for aurors as guards at Howard. It was incredibly hectic.

Auror Kwannon saw Pip arrive. She looked exhausted, her almond eyes heavy-lidded and face drawn. She was probably on her second or third straight shift, he thought, and brimming with tea to keep her sharp.

"Do you want me to spell you for a bit, Hedley?" he asked her, stepping over a merwoman as another auror put a poultice of sullyflower to the being's gills, so the stunned creature could breathe. There were several people in odd Muggle clothes on gurneys nearby - Muggles or Squibs.

Kwannon shook her head. "Go report to Kraeme. I'm fine." She paused. "Wait, this just came in," she said, pulling a sealed parchment from her belt. "You'll save me a trip… give it to the Tower."

Some people were made of bloody iron, Pip reflected. He nodded respectfully, taking the parchment, and walked through the golden portal into the Tower, moving briskly through the Thieves' Downfall.

Britain, Italy, Germany, Norden, France, the Free States, Nigeria, and half a dozen more states… their dying and desperately diseased streamed into the Tower all around Pip. He was back in the beating heart of the world once more. His chest swelled with pride, though he knew that was silly. He was just a small part of it. But to be here, now… being sent personally on missions for the Tower!

The clinic was bursting, Pip could see from his brief glance inside. Temporary bunks had been set up along the walls to accommodate those patients who had been healed and were just waiting on their dismissal, each one tagged with labels indicating time and healer. The special ward had been reclaimed for general use - apparently lycanthropes and vampires were being asked to come in another day. The discharge ward was a madhouse, as the Obliviators had set up shop in one corner and were carefully keeping tabs on all the Muggles, double-checking with the arithmancers on duty throughout the Tower to make sure no one fell through the cracks.

Pip headed down the corridors away from the hellacious racket, past the Conjuration Conjunction, the Extension Establishment, and Material Methods. J.C. wasn't in the meeting room, so he went down another corridor to Pairing Partnership. That was where the Tower had been spending a lot of time over the past few weeks, and J.C. Kraeme was probably with him.

"J.C.?" he asked, as he entered the Pairing Partnership. The Lovegood Leaf rustled as he opened and closed the door. There was a hum and a whirring in the room, which was filled with all sorts of esoteric Muggle equipment, but it wasn't very loud, and J.C. noticed him immediately. She was standing next to the Tower, who was on a computer (as usual). Luna Lovegood and Dolores Umbridge were also present, fiddling with odd objects.

As Pip approached Mr. Potter and J.C., he glanced at the screen, but the glowing text was written in a kind of code to hide its meaning:

else if(state==ENDQUOTE) {

state=QUOTE;

eeg_data[j][k++] = csv_line[i];

"Pirrip. Any problems today?" J.C. asked, her voice sharp. Her mess of black curls didn't hide the grim intensity of her scrutiny. She was one of the old breed, like Kwannon… before the ranks of the aurors doubled in 1996. Mr. Potter didn't look up - he just kept manipulating the computer's keys. He was wearing Muggle clothing - a brown suit. Very handsome, even with the ponytail.

"Not a one," Pip said, brightly.

Mr. Potter leaned back in his seat, and swiveled to face Pip. "What did the centaurs have to say?"

"I wasn't sure about most of it, sir. A lot of arguing over how things were said. But there was an elder there who could talk straight, and he was just happy that the new Tower rules for rejuvenation weren't going to 'intrude' on them," Pip said.

Mr. Potter smiled coldly. "Ah, yes. They keep their hands off of me and mine as much as they can. They don't want to be involved, since they fear some sort of moral Anns test. In their minds, they're not morally culpable for outcomes, as long as they remain uninvolved. An odd sort of moral calculus, but that's one of the flaws of deontology."

Oh, good, this again. At least I'm used to him saying impenetrable things.

"They get what they deserve, though… nasty creatures are sentencing themselves to their own punishment," said Miss Umbridge. It was odd to see her, here… one of the only middle-aged people who worked in the Tower or with the Unspeakables who hadn't been rejuvenated. She was plump and shiny and unpleasant, wearing a fluffy pink cardigan.

"There's probably a better explanation," Miss Lovegood said. The blonde witch had an odd-looking bonnet in her hands. "Blibbering Humdingers, rampant gum disease, a sustained private propaganda campaign… could be anything." She paused. "Although the last one of those is most likely."

"What on earth is a Blibbering Humdinger?" asked Miss Umbridge, with a sweetness that covered her contempt with a thin layer of syrupy falseness.

"It's a dreadful Dark creature that infects you when you're young," Miss Lovegood replied, turning back to the Muggle-made bonnet in her hands and fixing a metal wire into it. She sounded vague and airy. "It can control your behavior. Its life-cycle involves small animals, and so when the Humdinger takes over, it makes you unbearable to be around for other people. So you spend your time around small animals, instead."

Miss Umbridge snorted derisively and shook her head.

"You haven't been rejuvenated, though, Dolores," said Mr. Potter, swiveling his chair to face her, now. He was grinning at what Miss Lovegood had said. "Aren't you sentencing yourself to the same fate as the centaurs, eventually?"

"Well," Miss Umbridge said, pursing her lips. "I just haven't done it yet. I'm quite young and in vigorous health. And I'm not entirely sure about the whole thing, anyway. I don't think it's been thought through…" She paused, nervously. "That is to say, I'm just waiting."

"You have proven to be invaluable, Dolores, so please don't wait forever. You remind me of a certain journal editor I once knew, although you are less particular about the color of ink." Mr. Potter said, and smiled affectionately. He turned to Pip. "Mr. Pirrip - sorry, do you mind if I call you 'Pip?' "

Pip felt such a warm glow of pride that it threatened to stifle him, but he managed to say, "Please do, sir."

"Pip, have you heard anyone talking about the 'Three' today? Or about new and powerful magic they've seen? A new sort of Dark Mark, that wipes memories? You get along very well with everyone, and people talk around you… did you hear anything like that?"

"The 'Three,' sir?" Pip scratched his head. "I'm not sure… you mean the Shichinin?"

"No, not Neville and the twins," Harry said, shaking his head. He grinned again. "Although that would be a particularly terrifying possibility. Just keep your ears open, will you?"

Pip nodded, puzzled. "Yes, sir." He started, remembering. "Oh, sir, Auror Kraeme gave me this for you."

J.C. scowled ferociously at Pip as he handed over the sealed parchment. The Tower took it and broke the seal, scanning the contents rapidly. "Cappadocia and the Sawad appear to be in secret negotiations over a treaty," he mused. "It'll be in the Prophet tomorrow."

Miss Lovegood looked up, surprise wiping away her dreamy expression. "They're joining the Treaty! That's wonderful, Harry! And… surprising!"

"A Treaty of Independence," said Mr. Potter. "With the Malfoys' organization. They're enlisting with the Honourable." He handed the missive to Miss Lovegood, and Miss Umbridge crowded next to her to read it, as well.

"What does this mean, sir?" asked Pip. He felt a small twinge of fear in his guts, but it was overwhelmed by awe and joy at his place in things.

"I'm not sure," said the Tower, and fell silent.

It was by far the scariest thing Pip had seen all day.

≡≡≡Ω≡≡≡

NOTE: This is the end of Arc 1 of "Significant Digits." The next chapter will go up in two weeks. It will be a flashback chapter, prior to the start of Arc 2.

It will be called "Azkaban."

Chapter 17: Brute Existent

Wiglaf maðelode, Wihstanes sunu:

"Oft sceall eorl monig anes willan

wræc adreogan, swa us geworden is.

Ne meahton we gelæran leofne þeoden,

rices hyrde, ræd ænigne,

þæt he ne grette gold-weard þone,

lete hyne licgean, þær he longe wæs,

wicum wunian oð woruld-ende;

heold on heah gesceap.

Wiglad, son of Weohstan, spoke:

"Often when one man follows his own will

many are hurt. This happened to us.

Nothing we advised could ever convince

the prince we loved, our land's guardian,

not to vex the custodian of the gold,

let him lie where he was long accustomed,

lurk there under earth until the end of the world.

He held to his high destiny.

Beowulf

≡≡≡Ω≡≡≡

From the desk of the Tower Clinic Ombudsman:

To Whom It May Concern:

I would like to register an official complaint regarding the behavior of Owen Wilifred, a healer in your employ whom I had the misfortune to encounter this past October. I raise bicorn for a living, and do it better than anyone else in the Hollow. Even the Jugsons bought extract from me exclusively, and I daresay their Polyjuice and Waggum Potions lasted a fair bit longer than they'd have done if they'd bought off of old Weatherbee. But when I was a younger man, I was stabbed through the hand by one of the beasts. St. Mungo's mucked up the healing charm, and it's ached every winter since. So I was pleased to hear about the rejuvenation up at the Tower that the Boy-Who-Lived was offering.

I went to the Godric's Hollow Safety Pole and had myself checked out by the folks there, and then touched the thing and winked right out. Next thing I know, I'm on a bed and this squirrely-looking bloke is sitting there and watching me. He and another fellow ask me a whole mess of queer questions and put me through my paces on my history, and then they start poking me. I had brought a portrait of mine that's very well-done, good light and a good movement on it, but they barely glanced at it. They just babbled some nonsense. I checked my pockets before I went in, and it's a good thing, because I found a Galleon on the floor under me, that they'd arranged to have fall there so they could get it later. I wasn't born yesterday, nor the day before, and I know how to run a proper swindle. I wouldn't have minded paying, which is why I brought the money, but I can't stand a swindle. This Wilifred (I got his name before I left) wouldn't knock off the trick he was talking about… this whole German swindle of "the beat ease." He made me sit while he put his wand to my chest and did not do a bloody thing! I am no fool, and I know well enough that I'm not as hale as a young man. But slowing down a bit and getting glasses is normal, and I've always been a bit thin. It was the insult I resent! Mr. Wilifred didn't proper respect me, and I haven't spent fifty years building up the best bicorn in Britain just for some young swindler to try to pull the wool over my eyes. He was softening me up and would've asked for the deed to me house in return if he hadn't seen I wasn't going for it.

I got my Galleon back, shook Mr. Potter's hand, and got out of there. And never you mind the money, and I am sure full grateful about the hand, which is much better. Having that pain away has quickened my step, I'll tell you. But I would like to complain in full about Mr. Wilifred, who you should sack right away. The lad is a swindler.

Sincerely,

J. Ymir Ytterbar

Ytterbar's Bicorn

≡≡≡Ω≡≡≡

If the Tower has done the world any favors, it might be in uniting so many against him. By attempting to remake everything in his own cruel image, Harry Potter has made allies of enemies and friends of foes. And what is more, he has done this throughout the whole world. The ranks of those who sympathize with the global resistance to his tyranny - a group that is now known as the "Honourable," I admit with a blush - come from every walk of life.

In Britain, those who defended the traditional rule of noble houses are joined with those who advocated for Muggle-style elected houses… for neither party could accept a brash new boy-dictator, whose claim to power lies only in force.

In the Orient, those who have railed against the traditional British leadership in the Confederation are joined with those sought closer alliance with it, since the strength of British dominance in that body is irrelevant if the dominance is founded on intimidation and bloodshed.

In the Americas, the outright violence done by Harry Potter with a Muggle weapon in an attack on an old institution - an attack falsely done in my name, though no one can name why I would do this! - will bring together Americans of every stripe, rebelling against their Imperiused leadership.

Unless someone stops the Tower, then he will soon rule the whole world, crushing it in the grip of the porcelain automatons that replace those poor victims who go to be "rejuvenated." Independence should be no threat to anyone… anyone who does not plan to rule the world as its master, that is.

Excerpt from "Needful Allies," by Draco Malfoy

Unbreakable Honour

Vol 4 (1999), Issue 10

≡≡≡Ω≡≡≡

"Everyone's here, so I think we can get started," said Harry, as Diggory briskly walked in, a manila folder in hand. Auror Kwannon followed him, a stack of parchments in her arms.

The Chief Auror and Head of the DMLE, who was late, smiled and shrugged as he sat down at the meeting table. "Sorry, everyone. Emergencies today… two attempts on the Unspeakables, yesterday and today. Someone tried to Imperius Geraldine, and we discovered an outstanding theft from the vaults. Anyone have a copy of the agenda?"

Harry nodded, and slid a parchment over to him. "I can help you on the theft, I think… but we'll get to that one later."

Harry had found that it was important to have an agenda and stick to it - no chit-chat or the like - otherwise these meetings sprawled out of control, and nothing got done. A high-level meeting was seldom the best place for open discussion or brainstorming solutions; they were for sharing information and making decisions.

Administrative skills were a bigger part of his life than he'd ever thought they would be. He had four regular meetings a week - a faculty meeting with the Tower School of Doubt, a meeting with the heads of research (not all of them… the twenty-five departments were consolidated into four different groups), a meeting with the Tower clinic healers and aurors (technically it was the John Snow Center for Medicine, but not even Harry used that name at this point), and this one: the meeting with Magical Britain's Powers That Be.

And none of those even touched his other ventures, such as managing his money and charities (his current assets were now equivalent to that of a small country, quite literally), or teaching, or other pet projects. And the time he didn't spend doing that he was spending with Hermione or the Shichinin or Moody.

For someone who'd spent most of their boyhood in a relatively solitary and frustrated existence, he'd somehow transformed into a man who spent most of his life managing people. It would be so much easier if they would just do what he said… he could do ten times as much if he didn't have to argue… so many more people could be saved...

That's a Voldemort thought, he considered. Short-sighted and stupid. Whatever benefits in efficiency and speed I might gain, I would lose the benefit of other people's ideas and opinions if began to command rather than manage… and the entire point of our increasing democratic reforms, with the Tribunes and so on, is to employ the wisdom of crowds while providing more opportunities for outliers in achievement to rise in station. And if you're going to build a merit-based democracy, you'd better start at home.

Harry looked around the table. Cedric Diggory and Hedley Kwannon for the DMLE, Amelia Bones for the Wizengamot and Confederation, Percy Weasley for the Ministry, Simon Smith for the Returned (since Hermione was busy), Haddad and Podrut for the goblins (and a general outsider perspective), and Mafalda Hopkirk for the Unspeakables. They'd need to get someone from the Council over here, soon, to speak for Hig.

"Percy, would you start us off?" Harry said, glancing at the serious-looked redhead.

Weasley cleared his throat and glanced down at the parchment in front of him before beginning.

"We've gotten a few of the integration facilities in operation already. The logistics weren't very difficult, thanks to the help of some people from the Obliviator squads. They have a lot of experience in sanitizing contact between the two worlds." He glanced down at the parchment in front of him. "I promoted Klaus Gage to head of one of the squads, based on his performance. I think it might make sense to have that squad start to specialize in deliberate contact, like these facilities." Weasley looked up at Harry again, questioningly. "Since I assume we'll be scaling this up in the future…?"

Harry nodded. "Yes. Make a note, though… we need a better name for the program. 'Integration facility' makes us sound like we're… I don't know, Morlocks or something. These are restaurants and movie theatres." His hair was loose, and he pushed it back behind his ears absent-mindedly as he spoke.

"Music should be the next, I think, Mr. Weasley" said Mafalda Hopkirk, and the Senior Undersecretary nodded respectfully. The Venerable Unspeakable looked to be a voluptuous twenty years old, but still managed an air of authority when she spoke. It must be an acquired skill or habit, Harry reflected, since - according to most standards - her appearance no longer matched her gravitas. Ample décolletage, blonde hair, and blue eyes… but when she snapped at her subordinates, they jumped to obey like she was Merwyn the Malicious. It would probably be too much to hope that basic expectations had actually changed… that the society of Magical Britain had really begun to adjust to rejuvenation in a fundamental way. That would come in time.

"For right now, both restaurants and the theatre are losing money, hand over fist. Only moderate patronage, but high costs for wages, security, and so on. But we expected that." Weasley glanced at his notes again. "Oh, yes, one thing that should help is that Sylvia de Kamp just did a feature on Siegfried's for American Mage, and The Daily Prophet will be carrying it, as well. Apparently she was astonished, and she spends a thousand words in rapture over her 'adventurous Muggle dining experience.' "

"I went there," Chief Goldsmith Haddad said. "Had some beef. Quite tasty, I must say." Everyone at the table generally understood that this was both explicit approval of the restaurant and implicit approval of its inclusive policies towards potential patrons. Veauregard's Victuals, the leading fine dining establishment in Diagon Alley, did not permit goblins or any other Beings on the premises (except for the house elves that prepared the food).

Bones said nothing, but her lips grew tight. That discomfort wasn't unexpected, after having spent so much time with her. Even people we like and admire are products of their environment. It doesn't matter if she particularly likes the idea, as long as she intellectually accepts and agrees not to oppose the mingling of wizards and Beings. Many people have racist grandparents, but that doesn't make the grandparents bad people unless they're actively doing racist things - at least when we're speaking about "bad" and "good" in terms of preference utilitarianism. Having irrational or evil instincts or subconscious beliefs doesn't make you irrational or evil, if you don't act on them.

In fact, he considered, her beliefs might make Amelia a particularly good person. She's uncomfortable with some of the more personal aspects of this equality movement, like the idea of her niece dining at the same table as a goblin, or bringing them into the government and working with them so closely, but she overrules her baser instinct and does the right thing anyway. She might always be awkward around Haddad, Podrut, Urg, or the others, but she's being as good as she can be.

"Moving on," said Weasley, "I am unhappy to report that an envoy from the Strategos of Cappadocia paid me a visit last week, demanding I put him on the schedule for Minister N'Goma. I obliged, of course, but discussed the purpose of his visit a bit."

Simon Smith, a fleshy Scot and one of Hermione's Returned, leaned forward and rested his elbows on the table. He looked evenly at Weasley with flat brown eyes, emotional but somehow hollow, and said evenly, "Nikitas Seyhan."

"Of course it's bloody well Nikitas Seyhan," snapped Bones at the same time Weasley, more mildly, said "Yes, that's-"

There was a brief pause as each waited for the other to continue. Bones crossed her arms and only frowned. With her tight brown bun, it made her look severe. Weasley continued, his mouth twisting slightly in amusement at her outburst.

"Yes, the Seyhan fellow. He broke the Statute of Secrecy, they claim, and they're arguing that we're in violation of the Statute if we don't return him home, to be punished in accordance with Clauses 74, 75, and 76."

Harry didn't know the International Statute of Wizarding Secrecy in detail; he glanced at Bones and Haddad in succession to invite their interpretation. Bones had decades of experience in its international application, and Haddad was a trained lawyer with almost as much knowledge of how the Confederation acted to enforce it.

They glanced at each other, and Haddad spoke up. He tapped a finger thoughtfully on the table. "Probably a good case for it. You're - we're - sheltering Seyhan, and his sentence wasn't finished. It is a way for the Independents to attack under cover of law. I suppose that Germany or Norden could have made the same complaints at any time, but… well, Cappadocia was the first overtly disagreeable place that the Returned have struck."

"Surely we have the votes to simply ignore them… Madame Bones?" said Diggory. "Could we win an arbitration vote in the Confederation?"

"Easily," said Bones. "But it would cost us in public perception… particularly in the Ten Thousand. The Westphalians will use it against us to demand even more concessions. And it might complicate matters with Kenya… after the Free States and Nigeria joined the Treaty for Health and Life, Kenya opened up a dialogue on the quiet with one of our Confederation delegates, looking for, ah, 'considerations.' But major controversy or the appearance of lawlessness might drive them away. They wouldn't join the Independents, I don't think, but… well, it would be a setback."

The Treaty of Independence was still limited in its scope to a handful of states, fortunately: Cappadocia, Caucasus, most of the Sawad, and Russia. It was an idea borrowed from Muggle politics - actually, borrowed from Harry himself, in terms of the Cold War.

In the early days, when Draco had been working on planning for the future with Harry and Hermione, Harry had once floated the idea of including a mutual-defense pact in the Treaty for Health and Life - a way to dramatically raise the stakes in case of potential conflict. Now the Honourable were using it to set a tone of heroic defiance and to unite opposition to the Health and Life programmes. It had given the Council of Westphalia - or their puppets in the American governments, anyway - even more leverage in the ongoing negotiations, since it provided a viable alternative to what might otherwise seem an inevitable eventual outcome.

"Seyhan is at Powis?" Harry asked Simon. The Returned nodded. "How would Hermione feel about returning him to Cappadocia, if necessary? Their Dementors are gone… he would presumably be going into their normal prison."

"If he chooses to go, he may. But we won't return him against his will." Simon said. He didn't emphasize his words or raise his voice. This was an old problem that had started the moment Azkaban fell: Hermione believed the Dementation was punishment enough for any conceivable crime, and had unilaterally declared that those who had come back from that hell would always have a place with her.

It wasn't that Harry disagreed about Azkaban or the Dementors, of course: they had been vile beyond words, and no one - literally no one - deserved to be tortured to death in that way. He'd agreed unhesitatingly to her declaration. The ones she'd personally rescued had mostly been institutionalized, except for Odette Charlevoix, and many of those who had been transferred to Britain's remaining prison, the Howard House of Reform, had simply served out their relatively short sentences and had gone free without controversy. Others, though… well, Simon himself, for example, was a convicted murderer… but once he'd regained enough sanity to function, he'd walked free, and joined the newly-formed Returned.

In the months afterward, they'd taken a beating in public opinion for freeing so many criminals. Some people, like Walden Macnair, had been apparent successes - Macnair lived a quiet life enchanting broomsticks, now - but others had returned to fraud, robbery… or worse activities.

After a time, Harry had proposed new trials and mundane prisons for people like Charlevoix and Simon. Hermione had flatly rejected it, even after Harry pointed out that every month that this cost them in advancing their plans, politically, was another month during which people would die.

"It would save lives," Harry said. "It's cold, I know, but if giving Seyhan back to Cappadocia would improve our image with Kenya and the Ten Thousands, and speed things up with the American states, that's… hundreds of lives." He did some rough calculations in his head. Seventy thousand wizards or so in the United States… death rate in magical societies in the developed world was usually about four deaths a day for every thousand people... "In the United States alone, something like… three hundred wizards die every day. Every day matters."

"Every person matters," Simon replied. But he wasn't really arguing, since he would never countermand Hermione. Like the rest of the Returned, he would have cut off his hands if she'd told him to. Harry would have to wait to speak to her directly, if he wanted to change her mind. Not that it would do much good.

≡≡≡Ω≡≡≡

"Imagine if you had to choose between someone being tortured for fifty years," Harry said to Hermione. "Or a billion people getting a dust speck in their eye for a second, irritating them for an instant. No, not a billion… a googol people getting a dust speck. That's-"

"Ten with a hundred zeroes after it," Hermione interrupted. "And you want me to choose which of those would be the better outcome?"

"Yes. You have to weigh the aggregate discomfort of so many against the torture of one. If a googol isn't enough, make it a googolplex… ten to the googol power people."

"There aren't a googolplex of atoms in the galaxy, I wouldn't think, much less a googolplex of people," Hermione said, thoughtfully.

"Yes, but it's a number so big that it makes us confront our scope insensitivity. You don't picture an individual or even a crowd… you think about the numbers rationally, instead. A staggering amount of minute pains outweighs the suffering of any one person."

"Careful, Harry. You could justify a lot with that reasoning. And the answer is no. Charlevoix is going back to France, to visit her children. They want to see her, and she's going to try to find some connection to them… maybe recover some memories of them, if possible. She'll be meeting with people in their Ministry of Magic, too… might help with getting them to join the Treaty, someday."

"We could wait for her to come back. And it would be a fair trial."

"That will be her choice. She'll have a place with me, otherwise, until she chooses to go. She's paid any debt she might possibly owe the world… find another human sacrifice."

≡≡≡Ω≡≡≡

"Fine," Harry said to Simon, sighing. "I'll revisit this with the lady herself."

"We should muddy the waters, so it doesn't seem clear-cut," said Bones. "Give us something to talk about for our own part, when they bring this up. The son of the Strategos of Cappadocia was accused of breaking the Statute about a decade ago, as I recall… maybe that will work well."

"Sir? Sorry to interrupt," came a voice at the door. It was Auror Pip, pushing a hand truck. Standing upright on the truck and being wheeled along, frozen in place and stunned, was a thin-faced older man. Balding, but with great muttonchop whiskers. The man's face was frozen in a snarl, and his fingers were still curled around a now-absent wand, caught in the act of casting. There was a large bloodstain, still wet, on the man's thigh.

"That's Moody, yes," Harry said, smiling. "Good work."

Pip grinned - he'd gotten Mad-Eye Moody! Most of the Tower aurors had already done so - J.C. had gotten him eight times, now - but this was his first Moody. He drew his wand and dispelled the Stunning Hex. Pip couldn't wait to tell his mum.

Alastor "Mad-Eye" Moody's arms relaxed, and he worked his jaw experimentally for a moment. "Hell. This one got me?" His disguise - if a Transfigured body could be said to be a disguise - was a good one. He'd given Harry some pictures and instructions yesterday: this was another lycanthrope, but with space for a secret wand inside the thigh. A combination of prior attempts. Lycanthropes were still immune to the automatic stunning effect on the Safety Poles and Safety Sticks, so Moody had tried them for his intrusion attempts before, and he'd taken the Ultimate Ulna idea from Hermione.

"Yes, sir," said Pip, brightly. He smiled broadly and nodded to Harry, and left the room to return to his post.

"So, Alastor… Pip stunned you, this time," Bones said. The young-looking witch was working to keep a straight face. "My, my."

Moody shuffled over to a chair and sat in it, gingerly, as if his bones hurt. "Didn't put much planning into this one… just standard… keep them on their toes," he said, in a hoarse voice. He shot Diggory a purposeful glance when he opened his mouth to speak. The Chief Auror thought better of it… though he couldn't stop from smiling. Everyone sat politely for a moment longer, while Moody sorted himself out.

"Well then, Mr. Moody," said Weasley. "We were just discussing the possibility of returning Nikitas Seyhan to Cappadocia, since they're making a bit of a fuss about it at the Confederation. Mr. Smith here, however, indicates that this won't be happening, so Madame Bones prop-"

"Pfah," snorted Moody. "You're all as sharp as blind-worms. Me sitting here like this, and you're worried about having to hand over a fugitive?"

Harry smiled suddenly, and leaned forward. "But if he minds?"

"How long was he there?" Moody asked.

"Oh! Yes!" said Bones, smiling as well. "Er… he was in Göreme for twelve years, I believe."

"Then any happy associations he had are long gone," replied Moody, "so I doubt he'll protest… if he's even fit to protest about anything at all, after twelve years."

Harry glanced around the table, noting some expressions of puzzlement and some smiles at the solution. He explained, "Moody is suggesting we simply change his face and say that we've lost track of him."

"Or, better yet," said Diggory, "hand over a fake corpse."

"The Optimates of the Eleusinian Mysteries once did that," said Haddad, in his accented English. "During the Social War… back when death dolls were undetectable. Wanted to keep the Muggles of the Latin provinces in check, and so they made a big show of parading some heroic wizard corpses all through the city. The actual wizards, still quite alive, attacked Paeligni. Didn't succeed - oppression seldom succeeds in the long run - but a clever trick."

Harry frowned at the goblin, and Mafalda Hopkirk broke her silence to mutter, "Subtle."

There was an awkward pause.

"Anyway, let's get some sort of plan in place there. Moody, you'll handle it?" Harry said, glancing over at today's Moody. The balding lycanthrope nodded, looking irritable. "Whatever we do," Harry continued, "I do think it's time to begin putting some distance between the Tower and the Returned."

Diggory nodded in approval. "You're anticipating more confrontation, and you want Ms. Granger to be able to act with a free hand." It was widely rumored that Cedric Diggory was infatuated with the Goddess, and had made several attempts to ask her out. Harry wondered if that might affect his judgment, but he still seemed to be thinking straight when it came to Hermione and the Returned.

"Yes, I think-" But Harry broke off what he was saying when Diggory and Kwannon, followed a second later by Moody and Smith, leapt out of their seats, springing to the two doors into the meeting room. Diggory and Kwannon went to one, while Moody and Smith went to the other. They'd slammed and secured and warded the doors in a matter of moments, and continued to cast wards as the other wizards and witches in the room - slower to react, and not privy to the signal that had alerted Diggory and Kwannon - joined them and began casting. Harry got out of his seat and drew his wand, but remained away from the doors.

The spells were already thick within the Tower, and there was only so much more magical security that could be had, and so it was only a few minutes before the aurors, Smith, Bones, and Weasley were assuming battle positions, standing in spots staggered around the room, in a pattern designed to avoid most effective area spells. Diggory felt free to pull out his auror mirror, then, and bubble the guards on the inner door. He held the mirror so that most of the people in the room could see it.

"Kraeme, report."

Auror J.C. Kraeme's face appeared in the mirror. She looked calm. "Intrusion in the Receiving Room, sir. We've sealed the Tower entrance, and no attempt has been made on it. They're still fighting - we can hear it from here."

"Put the bubbler on a chair or something, J.C.," said Diggory. "Leave it open, so we know what's going on, but keep your eyes on that door."

The perspective of the bubbler - which looked like nothing so much as one of the small mirrored compacts that Muggles use for makeup - shifted and moved around, and finally settled at a level that looked waist-high to Auror Kraeme and Auror Pip, the entrance guards. It showed the entrance to the Tower, but the golden door had been completed obscured by a huge and heavy-looking silver plate, ornately decorated, that had been rolled into a frame in front of the entrance. Harry glanced over at Podrut, and smiled despite the tension to see the obvious pride on the goblin's face. He'd made the security hatch.

Everyone waited, tensely. Moody stood in a corner, his wand pointed towards one of the doors... and towards everyone else in the room ("I know a traitor will eliminate the biggest threats first, and you're the best avenue of attack," is how he had once explained it, after he and Harry had gone into lockdown earlier this month, during a similar alert, and Moody had spent the entire time with his wand pointed at Harry.)

"Quiet out there, now," commented Pip, glancing back at the mirror. Kraeme quieted him with a harsh glance.

They had to wait. Very few methods of communication were possible between the Tower and the outside world. It was a security precaution, but it made moments like this one particularly tense.

After another ten minutes or so, a pattern of knocks was audible on the silver plate. Kraeme nodded to Pip, who approached it, and knocked several times. There were two knocks in response, and Pip visibly brightened. "It's correct," he reported to the senior auror, and she grunted in affirmation and turned towards the mirror for orders. "Today's pattern, sir."

"Open it up," replied Diggory. Pip nodded, and reached for the heavy latch that held the plate in place. Harry was going to agree and congratulate the two door guards on their caution, but found himself unable to say that - as though the words simply did not exist in English to express any such sentiment.

"Wait!" he choked out, instead. Pip's hand froze on the gleaming metal handle.

Harry turned to Moody, who had his wand pointing at him. "Moody, how often are the knocks changed?"

"Every month," said Moody. "I wanted every week, but training has gotten lax, and they kept mucking it up."

True, thought Harry, remembering. Cedric had complained that the Tower security was so redundant and required so many different, frequently-changing protocols, that they were spending entire days each month sorting through false positives. Security protocols were an investment like anything else, and there were diminishing returns. The fact that there seemed to be some sort of problem - since Harry's Unbreakable Vow wouldn't let him agree to opening the door - didn't necessarily prove Cedric wrong, either. After all, Moody still hadn't been able to get inside, and he'd been very motivated to embarrass Cedric and prove his point.

"And was it changed after the lockdown earlier this month - that time when you spent twenty minutes menacing me?" asked Harry, raising his eyebrows. He pulled a stretchy hair-tie from one pocket as he spoke, and put his hair in a ponytail.

"No," said Diggory, heavily, looking embarrassed. Auror Kwannon, standing near the door with him, looked pale.

Moody had a fierce look of triumph on his muttonchopp-whiskered face. "And here you were, all excited about Pip stunning me."

"Not now, Alastor," snapped Bones. Her attention was still fixed on the bubbler.

"Sir?" asked Auror Kraeme.

"Just a moment, J.C. I'll send my Patronus." Diggory replied. "Expecto Patronum!"

A silvery bat flapped into existence, shedding argent light on the tense faces within the meeting room. "Go and speak to Harry Madagascar in the Receiving Room, and ask him what is going on."

There was another long minute, then the bat swung back into the room, and spoke in the high-pitched voice of Auror Herrera, "We gave the correct knock, Mr. Diggory, I'm sure of it. The situation is under control."

"Bear back the words, 'Monkey monkey monkey,' " said Diggory to his Patronus.

"I like bananas, dress me like a doll," replied Herrera, after the glowing bat had made the trip and returned. It was the correct response.

Diggory looked to Harry, who nodded in approval, then he turned to the bubbler. "Open it up, Pirrip." There was still a risk, given the mistake in operational security this month, but the Thief's Downfall before the Tower entrance and the exceptional magical defenses of the facility were more than enough of a margin of safety.

Everyone relaxed a little, only to tense up again in a moment, as another sharp report came through the bubbler.

"There are prisoners!" shouted Kraeme. "And they're students!"

Chapter 21: Bonus: Shichinin

April 15th, 1999

Luuq, Somalia

"Drop your guns!" shouted Neville, leaping through the window.

"Guns are stupid!" shouted Fred, leaping in next to him.

"Your mother is a hamster and something something elderberries!" shouted George, leaping in at Neville's other side.

"That's not even close to being right, George! Extinctus!" said Neville, as he swept his wand across to one of the eight soldiers.

The soldiers were tough: hardened Ogaden warriors who had been fighting for years. It would be hard to say what their cause really was: independence for their clans; the unity of the Ogaden regions in Somalia and Ethiopia; or personal power. But whatever the cause, they had spent most of their recent time intimidating, beating, or shooting the residents of local villages. They were hard men, and used to violence. And so while they were surprised when white men in black dresses jumped through the window and began waving sticks, there was an easy solution at hand. They raised their rifles.

Click. Click. Click. Click. Click. Click. Click. Click.

The Extinguishing Charm suppressed small fires. That included small chemical fires. That included the ignition of the primer in the 5.56×45mm NATO cartridges in the soldier's guns.

The two worlds were separated, but not by that much. The Záh Kardja used flamethrowers during Grindelwald's War, and many wizards were constantly scrutinizing the Muggle world - if only so that they could disguise themselves better (or make ironic devices, like a lighter that turns off lights). Unfortunately for Smith and Wesson, guns happened to be unusually easy to disable with simple and quick magics.

"References are only funny-" said George.

"-if everyone is in on the joke," completed Fred. The twins snapped their fingers at the front and rear doors to the store, and both locks clicked audibly closed.

"The exact opposite is true… it's funnier if only a few people understand what's going on," retorted Neville. "Stupefy! Stupefy!"

"Iksa jir!" screamed one soldier, still pointing his gun at Neville and wildly pulling the trigger, even as two of his companions fell to the ground, shivering with red energies. A fourth soldier barked at another, "Wac caawimaad!", as he threw down his own gun and pulled a knife. It was a short blade with a tape-wrapped handle; the cutting edge was concave with long use and frequent sharpening. The Ogaden fighter hefted it lightly in one hand, and advanced, his face hard.

"Stupefy!" cast George and Fred in unison, and the knife-wielding soldier slouched sideways, stunned. Four of the five remaining soldiers dropped their guns and raised their hands, one pleading, "Joogso, sixir, joogso!" The fifth combatant appeared too terrified to do anything more than pull the trigger on his useless gun again and again.

The three wizards stunned them all, methodically and easily. The entire encounter was finished within a minute.

The work was easy, as it always was when the three magical knuckleheads zipped somewhere on the globe to be superheroes around Muggles. They were skilled Hit Wizards backed by the most powerful wizard and most powerful organization on the globe, and so naturally there wasn't much risk. If they did get in trouble, they'd teleport out and call in like… fifty more guys. It was like the SAS fighting toddlers, and the most serious danger to the trio was the terrible quality of their own jokes. Example: they'd called their trio the "Shichinin" (七人, or "Seven People") because they really loved a Kurosawa movie Harry had once shown them, and because Fred and George were certain that "our enemies will think there's four more of us somewhere!"

After they'd finished stunning the soldiers, Neville, Fred, and George took their guns and ammunition, feeding them into pouches designated for that purpose (whose extra-dimensional space must be positively bulging with tens of thousands of pounds' worth of armaments at this point), and Fred bubbled an Obliviator squad. It wasn't that the three of them couldn't have done the False Memory Charms, of course, but rather that the professionals had enormous experience in designing plausible multi-cultural explanations for bewildering events. They could even design the new memories to serve a larger purpose. In this case, the new memories would encourage these soldiers to abandon armed conflict and take up a peaceful political movement within Muggle Somalia.

The Obliviators were quite good at handling these situations. The usual method was to create a tragic and deeply affecting past event, prolonged discussion, and personal agreement for each participant. In Kosovo, the Obliviators had helped the Shichinin turn an entire division of the State Security Service of Yugoslavia away from violence by crafting a fictional encounter where two of their armed squads were ordered to kill an Albanian family who'd refused to leave their home. A little girl from the family made an impassioned speech and offered them flowers, instead, and all the members of that squad remembered being moved to tears and vowing to preserve the lives of the people above all else.

Harry had called it "weaponizing cognitive dissonance" when he'd given them their mission, after a considerable speech about how it was monstrously unethical to simply ignore the massacres that took place on a regular basis in the Muggle world.

"These are fancy guns," said Fred, examining the last rifle. He'd grown to be tall and handsome, with a thick mop of reddish-brown hair and a strong jaw. "Very shiny and new." He threw it to George, who caught it and squinted at it closely.

"We've been seeing a lot of fancy guns, lately," said George, nodding. George had also grown to be tall and handsome, although - unlike his brother - he had a strong jaw and a thick mop of reddish-brown hair. He glanced at Neville. "Remember the guns we got off those fellows in Jijiga?"

Fred spoke to the pouch in his hand: "Gun from Jijiga warehouse." When a stock appeared at the mouth of the pouch, Fred grabbed it and pulled a rifle free. The mouth of the pouch chewed toothlessly at the gun as it emerged, the lips undulating around the weapon. It was a rifle just like the one in George's hand: matte black metal with a plastic-looking black stock. It looked much more modern than the cheap Chinese or Eastern European guns they usually found (mostly AK-47s or variants).

Neville sat on a stack of plastic-wrapped soda flats, frowning. "Where is the ONLF getting these guns?"

"Let's ask them! Fred, do you speak Somali?" asked George.

"Why no, George. Say, do you speak Somali?" said Fred.

"I used to, Fred, but I'm afraid being forced to watch boring movies where mustachioed men bang coconuts together has quite driven it out of my head," said George, sadly.

"That's a shame, George."

"A terrible tragedy, Fred."

"Maybe quoting constantly about dead parrots will help bring the knowledge back, George."

"Why of course, Fred! That's the ticket! That won't be extremely annoying at all!"

"You just don't appreciate true genius," said Neville, sourly. The wiry young man had a prominent nose and flashing green eyes. He gestured for the rifle, and George threw it over to him. Neville spoke to his own pouch. "Gun encyclopedia."

"True genius is repeating the same 'nudge nudge wink wink' line over and over, George."

"Quite right, Fred! And singing songs about lumberjacks!"

"AK-101," said Neville, comparing a photograph in The Illustrated World Encyclopedia of Guns with the rifle in his hand. "Oh, bloody hell, it says that right on the barrel. And there's a date. 1999… these are brand new. 'ИЖМАШ'… these are Russian, not cheap knock-offs."

"The OLNF is getting monies from Egypt-" said Fred, more seriously.

"-but where did they find someone to sell them these?" said George.

"Those Eritrean blokes had fancy rifles, too. The ones shooting civilians in Maidema?" said Fred.

"Someone is aggravating these wars, on purpose or for profit," said George, scowling.

"You're thinking what I'm thinking?" Neville asked, feeding gun and book back into his pouch.

"Find the source of the fellow willing to sell the best hardware to the worst people-" said George.

"-and cut off the supply, and maybe his hands too-" said Fred.

"-and we might save a lot more lives," finished Neville.

≡≡≡Ω≡≡≡

April 3rd, 1999

Jijiga, Somali Regional State, Ethiopia

The rangeland surrounding the city of Jijiga was greener than it usually would have been; the drought had killed off eight of every ten grazing cattle, and the xerophytic acacia and crossberry on the gentle hills around the city had flourished in their absence. The warehouse was in a small complex of storage buildings to the north, past the airport and the dry riverbed. It was actually quite a pretty area - quiet, and far enough from the main city that there were almost none of the sun-bleached scraps of trash that were usually littered everywhere.

As they approached the building on foot, Fred and George paused to gather handfuls of crossberries, and some of the purple, star-shaped flowers. They would be a nice surprise for their mum. If there had been any observers, it would have looked an odd sight: the Shichinin were Disillusioned, and it would have seemed as though berries and flowers were vanishing into thin air, one by one.

Outside of their Mobile Mary, the trio was virtually always Disillusioned. It was an unfortunate necessity when working in any of the places in the world where white people were rare. There were other ways to avoid sticking out, of course, but this was the easiest.

Neville pushed open the simple door to the plain corrugated metal of the warehouse. It was unlocked, and the place looked deserted. The heavy metal shelves were mostly bare. The entire place appeared just as it had when they'd left a week ago, except that the four stunned guards and Obliviator squad had gone, and the eight crates of automatic weapons had been disposed of (the large crates being rather too inconvenient for the Shichinin to take care of themselves).

Fred and George made a beeline for the two old card tables that had been set up in one corner. They'd remembered that there had been some paperwork there - shipping forms and tariff slips. Ethiopia had strict import and export controls, as well as high tariffs. The two wizards found something that appeared to be a ledger, with numbers in columns that they guessed represented wholesale costs, shipping fees, tariffs, label numbers, and the amounts spent on bribes (considered a reasonable business expense here, indeed as in most countries). The shipments were mostly small, but a few shipments had big numbers - hundreds of thousands of birr, the local Muggle money. Not knowing how much the guns cost or the exchange rate for… well, anything to anything else, really… it was hard to figure out if these were the shipments they wanted.

"We better take this," said Fred.

"Maybe someone can sort it out for us later," agreed George.

They fed the ledger into Fred's pouch, and checked in with Neville. He wasn't inside, but they soon found him. He was sorting through discarded shipping crates. Most of them had been reused or repurposed, but some of them were broken or damaged along the joints, and had been tossed in a haphazard pile outside the warehouse. Many of the more robust crates had handfuls of moldy hay still inside of them, which had once kept contents dry and cushioned.

"Find anything?" he asked, as he shifted broken-sided crates around.

"A ledger for recording transactions, we think," said George.

"Maybe just looks like it, though," added Fred as an afterthought.

"Oh ho… creeping quackgrass!" said Neville, delighted. He snatched up a loose handful of of withered brown stalks from one of the crates.

Fred and George looked at each other, trying to decide if he'd made that up. They decided that he hadn't.

"Of course it is," said Fred.

"We were about to say the same thing," said George.

"Bleeding obvious it's quacking creepgrass," snorted Fred.

"Embarrassing you even have to say anything, really," laughed George.

"No… there's some Siberian Spurge in here, too… Euphorbia seguieriana," mused Neville. "I wonder if this is a different wheatgrass, other than quackgrass."

"What do you feed a boffin like this?" Fred asked George.

"Nothing, you just let them swot and change their litter regularly," answered George.

"Grass Genera," commanded Neville to his pouch. He sat down with the resulting The Grass Genera of the World, and got to work.

≡≡≡Ω≡≡≡

At least an hour and four games of gobstones later, Neville made a hooting sound of glee. "I have it, gentlemen!" He leapt to his feet, and trotted over to where Fred and George were squatting, flicking marbles on a chalked-up board. Fred looked up, wiping his face, and asked, "Oh, good, we were worried it would take forever-"

"-and be extremely boring to even think about," said George, scooping up the gobstones.

"This hay is from the Don River valley in Russia!" said Neville, grinning hugely. "The only place where any Agropyron grows with the Euphorbia seguieriana subspecies niciciana! It's… it's... " He grasped for some suitable word. "It's elementary!" he declared, after a moment, lamely.

It might seem unbelievable that anyone could be such a nerd.

And yet it's true.

"Then it's back to Abuja-" said Fred, referring to Nigeria's capital.

"-where we can catch a portkey back home for a nap and some brekkie," finished George, referring to rashers and eggs.

"And then: Russia!" declared Neville, relishing the idea. He triumphantly held a handful of moldy hay.

≡≡≡Ω≡≡≡

A nap and brekkie later

Main Office, Department of Magical Law Enforcement, Ministry of Magic, London

"Good evening, gentlemen," said Director Diggory. He was examining a map on the wall, tracing routes with his finger as he consulted one book plucked from a large stack, and occasionally sipping a large mug of tea.

The young man was only a few years their senior, and they'd all once gone to school together. The twins had even had a nickname for Cedric: "Pretty Boy Diggory." Director Diggory was aware of this, but - oddly - didn't find the name all that hurtful. He'd had to grow a thick skin, since he was in command of aurors decades older than him. Fortunately for him, there were few complaints by this point, six months into his command. He benefited from a great many factors: he was shockingly good at his job, he was blisteringly handsome in a way that made Madame Bones blush, he was personal friends with the Tower, and he was from a house so Noble and Most Ancient that the first Chief Auror had been named Eldritch Diggory (who had gone on to be Minister for Magic).

"We brought in a temporary Muggle expert with the usual procedure, and sorted some of this out," said Diggory, closing the book next to him and sitting at his desk. He brought his tea with him, setting it at his elbow. He picked up a sheet of parchment. "He's identified the source of that crate: an airport in Russia in a town called Mikhaylovka, by way of Veshenskaya."

"Ah, yes," said George, wisely.

"We summer there," said Fred.

"Lovely place," said George.

"Wonderful flowers," said Fred.

"Beautiful plumage," said Neville.

The twins groaned.

"You three go to Russia. Bring Bogdanov with you; she'll be able to help."

The twins groaned a second time, and George flopped dramatically forward onto Diggory's desk for a moment, leaning over the Director's tea with exaggerated despair. Ilya Bogdanov had been the head of the Office for the Detection and Confiscation of Counterfeit Defensive Spells and Protective Objects until recently. She had survived the great purge of the Ministry in 1994, probably as an attempt to conciliate the Malfoy faction by leaving one of their number in a position of power, but she'd burned through all of her chances to turn over a new leaf, and had been demoted. Percy had told the twins at family dinner one Sunday that Bogdanov had been lucky to keep any sort of job at all, since they'd had dozens of complaints about her attitude.

"That's enough," said Diggory, scowling. "None of you knows Russian or Russian. Bogdanov speaks eight languages, and grew up with Russian. She went to Durmstrang, too, and most of the people now in charge there were her classmates. If you want to do this thing, tracking down guns in one of the Independent states, you're taking her. Things are too tense with them right now, politically... we don't want to push them further away thanks to some idiots meddling in their affairs without a guide. I don't care what you think of personality. Take her… otherwise, you're off to Yemen, tout de suite!"

The Shichinin grumbled as they walked down the hall to the elevators, to head down to the ODCCDSPO's overflow offices.

"She's a pureblood fanatic from Russia who graduated Durmstrang, loves Malfoy, and just got demoted," said Neville, glumly. "We'll be there ten minutes before she stuns us in the back and feeds pieces of us to snargaluffs."

"All the more reason to take her along-" said George.

"-and expose her as a traitor," said Fred.

"But we'll be in pieces inside of snargaluffs!" objected Neville.

"When else will we have the opportunity to flush her out? She's kept her head down since she lost her position to Covenant, keeping quiet. Probably spending her time sending detailed reports to Narcissa and Draco Malfoy," said Fred.

"And relaxing in her off-hours, painting a series of tasteful landscapes in the blood of muggleborns," said George.

They stepped onto the elevator, accompanied by a flurry of interdepartmental memos that circled busily overhead, and hit the button for the fourth level. Almost half of all DMLE and DMAC (Department of Magical Accidents and Catastrophes) offices were now on other floors, since the second and third floors were full. Aurors and arithmancers and a few other professions had done very well in the Ministry, of late. Fortunately, there was room to spare, since middle management and licensing boards and regulators had been decimated. The entire games division had simply been sacked in 1995, after losing half their staff the year before.

Fred knocked on Bogdanov's door when they arrived there, calling out, "Hello? Madame Bogdonov?"

"Come," said a sharp voice, and George opened the door.

"Hullo, Madame," said Fred to the older witch who was sitting at a desk inside the cramped and dark office. "The Director sent us… he was wondering if you would lend us a hand with an excursion?"

Agapa Ilyichna Bogdanov put down the parchment in her hands, looking at the Shichinin coolly. She was perhaps a hundred years of age, with grey hair kept in a short pixie cut. She was one of a shrinking percentage of older Ministry workers who hadn't taken advantage of rejuvenation, and it showed: the skin hung loose at her neck but was taut on her face, and liver spots were visible on her thin hands. Her blue eyes were still sharp, though, as she regarded them with visible displeasure.

"Hullo, gentlemen. So two Weasleys and a Longbottom want me to go on an 'excursion?' " she asked. There was only a slight trace of a Slavic accent. "I don't know whether to be flattered or frightened."

"The Director has asked that you accompany us to Russia, Madame Bogdanov… we're trying to track down the source of some Muggle weapons," said Neville. "We were hoping to leave tomorrow morning, if that is possible. I hope you're not too busy?"

Bogdanov glanced at the parchment in her hands, and dropped it to the desk with a look of distaste. It fell among dozens of other sheets and forms. "I am not. They have put me in this dreary little office and set me to writing reports and giving depositions to the Wizengamot on counterfeit Safety Sticks and other such trivialities. It is busy work, nothing more. So no one in the department has to speak to me, you see." She collected parchments into a rough stack with a few aggressive movements, then dumped them in a pile to one side. "Why is the babe-in-charge interested in Muggle weapons?"

George explained, "Someone is selling powerful guns to some bad people in Africa - in Ethiopia - and it's making a few wars down there a lot worse. The Ogaden National Liberation Front and the Eritrean militia groups have been-"

"Wait… a wizard is selling Muggle weapons?" interrupted the witch, raising her eyebrows in surprise.

"No," said Fred. "It's probably a Muggle. But the ONLF and the Eritreans used to only have cheap old guns, and not many of them. Now they're better supplied, and it's showing in the civilian death toll down there."

"So a Muggle is selling Muggle weapons to other Muggles, and those Muggles are killing still other Muggles," said Bogdanov, rolling her eyes. "What is our concern?"

"That is our concern," said George. "A lot of people are being hurt-"

"-and we're in a position to stop it," said Fred.

"I know your little trio's mandate," said Bogdanov, rising to her feet and walking to the coatrack. She pulled down her cloak, and settled it over her robes. "But surely you don't waste your time pretending to be some sort of… Muggle aurors? What possible difference do you make, when they die like ants all day long?"

Fred and George glanced at each other. Their lips were tight. Neville hurriedly spoke up. "We've been making a lot of difference. We're mobile, we're effective, and we're stopping hundreds of future deaths every day."

"And why is that our responsibility? Are we Muggles, now?" she asked, fastening her cloak in place. "No, never mind. Spare me. I will go with you, no argument. Better than pushing parchment here. And it has been months since I was back home. Let us go make arrangements."

≡≡≡Ω≡≡≡

The limit on how far one could Apparate was a combination of the physical and metaphorical distance. Land's End to John o' Groats was a single trip for a native Englishman, but a Bulgarian attempting the hop had better have his three D's firmly in mind. Any trip of any considerable distance, then, required portkeys - for the sake of safety and brevity both. One of the great advantages enjoyed by Ministry officials - aurors and Hit Wizards included - was ready access to the Official Business desk at the Portkey Office. Further, the assistance of the Chief Mugwump of the International Confederation of Wizards, as well as the Tower (who had considerable influence in any Treaty state, such as Nigeria), eased any concerns about international travel. The Shichinin had been extremely fortunate in their friends, as events would have it… perhaps anyone in close proximity to figures of mighty destiny would have a tendency to get caught up in orbit, swirling around in the eddies of fate.

The Shichinin, accompanied by Bogdanov, who had humorlessly told them to call her "Ilya," were soon on their way, whisked by portkey to the closest available destination to Mikhaylovka: Volgograd.

Truth be told, the portkey - the stiff and filthy cover of an old library copy of a Muggle book named Battlefield Earth - came from a box labeled "Tsaritsyn," but that was nearly a century behind the times. Muggle names changed too frequently for the Portkey Office to worry about, and they made do with a huge blackboard scrawled with guides to the current nomenclature. Really, the Shichinin had gotten lucky that Russia was relatively stable: some Muggle areas were so prone to changing their names that the Office had given up. After Herzegovina's Tomislavgrad changed its name for the fourth time in a century (Duvno became Tomislavgrad became Duvno and then finally back to Tomislavgrad), the Office had stopped making portkeys for the city entirely.

It was a fairly long trip from London to Volgograd: 2,400 miles or so. They snapped the dirty piece of ruler in half, standing in the Ministry atrium off in a quiet one corner, and it felt as if a rope had been knotted around their waists and yanked violently, pulling them sideways and up and back and around. They whirled down to the ground and came to a staggering stop, but their feet sank into an inch of thick mud almost immediately. Neville waved his arms around wildly for a moment to keep his footing, his boots skidding a pace.

It was fairly cool, but not so cold that it was uncomfortable. Even here, spring was a pleasant time of year. They were in a building that was mostly empty, but which seemed to superficially resemble a barn (albeit with poor drainage). A ragged bulletin board, its lower edge looking as though it had been chewed upon, bore a few parchments stamped with the ornate crest of the Russian Oak. They were in the right place. The right muddy, run-down place. The right muddy, run-down, manure-strewn, dangerous-looking place.

"An hour and a half to Mikhaylovka," said Bogdanov, who was wrapping a scarf around her neck, having leaned her broom against the bulletin board. "We should go check in with the Domovoi here and then be on our way, if we wish to have a few hours of light when we get there. Bukavac live in the rivers and feed at night, so we should not linger. They feed on children." She glanced at her three youthful companions, who seem to have missed her implication as they buttoned mackintoshes over their robes. They only nodded, looking around warily.

The Domovoi was situated in the dirty brick Muggle civil services building, a disappointing distance away from the beautiful neoclassical City Duma. Most of the offices in the civil service appeared to have no function except to support an astonishing variety of people taking quiet naps. The Domovoi was one of these: a sleepy-looking little man with a wilting wet mustache, who unquestioningly stamped their documents and waved them on their way. He probably would have done the same if a trio of Voldemorts in fiery hats appeared in front of him with their own documents. It was comforting to know that there was some constancy in the world.

They kicked off from outside of the building within minutes, riding cruiser brooms that were comfortable for long hauls, but which could be adjusted for better speed and maneuverability if necessary (mostly a matter of aerodynamics and swapping out the forward hand-hold, to replace the Braking Charm with a version featuring tighter turns). They flew while Disillusioned, as standard procedure dictated. The invisibility might seem silly, especially when they left the last buildings of Volgograd far behind, and the only Muggle road wended its way in and out of sight among vast stretches of unpopulated wheatfields and steppes below, but time had proven its utility. The only annoying thing was the necessity to use minor charms to keep track of everyone's location, and the occasional confusion that resulted when someone fell behind (bathroom breaks were the usual culprit).

After a longish period of silence, Bogdanov drew her broom alongside Neville's, and called out a question. She had to raise her voice to be heard over the wind.

"Tell me something," she called. "Why are more Muggles a good thing?"

"What?!" replied Neville, unsure if he'd heard her correctly. He'd thought she had asked why more Muggles would be a good thing, but that was something a cartoonish sociopath would say.

"Why are more Muggles a good thing? You're interfering with their little wars to save them, and now we go to stop Muggles from selling Muggle guns to other Muggles. You're taking responsibility for them, like a shepherd. But shepherds have a very good reason for their work. What is your reason?"

There were spells to make this sort of chatting easier in the face of the wind, but Neville wasn't sure he wanted to be having this conversation at all, so he didn't cast any of them. "We're not shearing the Muggles, if that's what you're asking," he said.

"No, but you're making yourself their masters, which seems a curious thing for someone like you to do. To step in and say who should live and who should die - by virtue of where you intervene and where you do not - that is making choices for them, yes? And you are deciding as a principle that more Muggles is better. You want to stop them from being shot, yes?" Bogdanov sounded amused by the entire idea: Neville could imagine her sharp eyes as sardonic and mocking.

"Sort of," said Neville, after pausing to think. "It's more… if you have the ability to save someone's life - anyone's life - you should do it. And that's especially true when it's very easy." He pointed down to the ground below them, picking out a small lake from near its parent river as it passed beneath, then realized she couldn't see the gesture. "Like if there was a person down there in the pond, even a stranger, you would go and help them. That's still something you should do if the pond is a mile away, or a hundred miles away."

To Bogdanov's credit, she didn't answer right away, but actually thought about what she'd heard. This is rarer than one might imagine. Their brooms drifted apart. Eventually, though, she pulled back in close, and said, "I should think that it would be good if I could save the person, but it is not my duty. Not my job." Neville was going to reply, but she went on. "And if I save one person, then I would have to save the person in the next pond, yes? Otherwise I am deciding that the first person is better. Soon I am saving all the people in all the ponds… being able to do it makes it necessary, for you, yes? We do what we must, because we can?"

Neville had a ready answer for this, since he'd heard Hermione Granger talk about this with Harry. He shook his head, and called back, "No… you rescue as many people as you can, without ruining your own life. Doing the right thing can't mean destroying yourself."

"Can't it?" called back Bogdanov, maddeningly, and pulled her broom away. But Neville wasn't about to challenge his own conclusions just because this Russian witch was confusing contrariness for wittiness. He rolled his eyes and kicked his broom up another ten meters, pulling level with where his charm said the twins would be.

"Well, that was an unpleasant conversation," he said to the air.

"Tell me something, young man -" called George.

"- have you really never tried a fine filet of Muggle?" said Fred, smacking his lips noisily.

Bogdanov was left to fly alone the rest of the journey, while the Shichinin chatted about other ways to leverage their mission. The older woman might have meant to be nasty, but she'd brought to Neville's mind the possibility of force-multipliers. This single arms dealer could be - should be just the beginning of a new phase of their operations. It was widely known (widely rumoured, anyway) that Harry was engaged in all sorts of Muggle charity. Fred was friendly with a bloke who worked as an arithmancer at the Ministry, and it was apparently a pretty open secret that they were shipping out truckloads of advanced water filters, cooking stoves, and other goods. So Neville and the twins didn't think they'd step on his toes, there. But it would be quick and easy to smash up some weapons factories, for example. There were strict regulations about subverting Muggle politics, but none of the Shichinin could think of any legal, ethical, or practical objection to making sure that arms manufacturing suffered a brisk run of bad luck.

What could be wrong with that, really?

≡≡≡Ω≡≡≡

Bogdanov brought her broom up to their level, clicking at them four times. They all dropped their Disillusionment for the time being, and came to a halt. Fred leaned over and pulled a beetle out of Neville's hair, where the thing had become trapped at some point during the past hour or so.

"Mikhaylovka," Bogdanov said, pointing ahead. It looked like just larger version of some of the uninteresting grey Muggle towns they'd passed, but a brightly-colored banner was visible strapped to a grain elevator and labeled with blocky Cyrillic lettering - it must have meant something to Bogdanov.

Crescent lakes, reservoirs, and canals marked this southern side of the town, as well as some industrial-looking buildings to the east. Squat houses with fenced-in grounds surrounded one large lake directly in front of them, continuing off to the west.

Fred took out a pair of omnioculars, and scanned the town. Train tracks bisected Mikhaylovka - if the shipment of arms they'd tracked had needed to be moved about, before being loaded on a plane and sent on to Veshenskaya, that may have been how it had been done. Wordlessly, Fred held the omnioculars to one side, where George was holding out his hand.

"Not a lot of factories, here. Some other Muggle industries, but not a lot of manufacturing on a big scale," said George, peering through the device.

"Some places working with big piles of rock and sand, other places with grain silos and those trucks… not a lot of big factories," agreed Fred.

"It has been much time since Muggle Mastery for me," said Bogdanov, leaning forward on her broom and using one finger to push her hair off of her forehead. "What do you mean?"

"They're saying that the Muggle who shipped the guns to Africa probably wasn't selling them directly - whoever operates from here was a middleman. Like how Potage's doesn't make the cauldrons they sell… they buy them from craft-shops, instead," said Neville.

"Maybe the gun craft-shop is hidden here as something else," said Bogdanov. She might have been trying to be helpful, or she might have just enjoyed meddling.

Neville shrugged. "Maybe. But to run a place like that, you need lots of things from other Muggle places, I think. Hard to hide… and why bother?" He shook his head. "Plus, our current theory is that the whole thing is illegal, so we're really looking for a middleman, like Potage."

"Nip in the train station-" said Fred.

"-and have Madame Bogdanov chat with someone who might know?" said George, lowering the omnioculars and offering them to the Russian witch. She waved them away, and Neville swung his broom around to take them, instead.

"Sounds like a plan. Madame, if you're up for a quick chat and Confundus Charm? The airstrip here looks small, so if many heavy industrial crates, ones that may contain guns, have been trucked on out there from the train station over the past year, that's probably our guy. There shouldn't be that many… too expensive for most shipping." said Neville. "We find the source, and we've found our arms dealer… and whoever's stoking the flames in Ethiopia."

"Happily I will comply. Why so easy, though? Would this person not fear Muggle authorities?" Bogdanov said. They all began lowering their altitude, to bring themselves to a rest behind a deserted-looking grain silo.

"I don't think it's something they worry about here-," said George.

"-although Muggle politics are bloody insane, so who even knows." said Fred.

"So this isn't even a crime - selling the guns? You are happy to overrule their own leaders, and decide for them what should not be allowed, eh?" Bogdanov said, smiling and raising her eyebrows. "Makes sense to me, but it's surprising."

No one took the bait.

Landing on the ground, they stowed their brooms. Bogdanov didn't have Hit Wizard gear, but Fred had brought along an extra pouch for her to use as a convenience. It was actually very thoughtful of him; there were four loaner pouches in the DMLE, and he'd made sure he requisitioned the good one for her (the only one of the four that didn't stink of troll, for whatever reason). The four of them recast their disillusionment, sorted out who would lead the way with a clicker in hand, did some basic security scans to check if they were being observed, and got moving at a brisk walk.

The walk to the train station brought them almost all the way through Mikhaylovka, walking along the roads that ran next to the tracks. It seemed like the workday was winding down as the day itself waned; a scratching of cirrus clouds forming overhead helped darken the remaining daylight. Sunset proper wouldn't arrive for hours yet, but the streets were beginning to fill with people. It was only Thursday, but there were already some drinking parties audibly going on - the four wizards saw a sizeable contingent of men in overalls dusty with chalk, walking down the street with bottles in hand and enjoying the mild evening with a mellow song. Quite a nice town, really.

The train station had tall fences and some guards posted, but it was easy enough to stroll past the tollbooth and duck under the barrier arm. Bogdanov took the lead once they were up onto the rust-streaked concrete slabs of the platform, clicking three times to signal she wanted to take charge. She glanced at the signs invisibly and led them with intervals of clicks past pallets stacked with plastic sacks of concrete, forklifts, piles of rough-barked ties, and the other machinery necessary for a rural freight. Two trains were being loaded with containers of crushed rock, via slow and painstaking maneuvers with short cranes. A lot of yelling was apparently essential to the process.

Bogdanov paused in front of a red-painted door with squat green Russian words on it, and clicked four times. The four of them dispelled their Disillusionment once more, and the Shichinin followed her wordlessly into the office.

"Confundo. Инспекция!" said the Russian witch to the pot-bellied man in grey coveralls standing in front of a cheap plastic filing cabinet. "Я нуждаюсь в ваших записей на поставки в взлетно-посадочной полосы."

The man blinked rapidly past a pair of thick bifocals, but eventually shook his head as though to clear it, and answered hesitantly, "Конечно. Все в порядке, инспектор." He leaned down and opened the bottom drawer, drawing out a file folder and offering it to her. Its label had been scribbled out and rewritten at least five times. "Есть только несколько договоров такого рода…"

"Были ли какие-либо большие ящики груза?" asked Bogdanov, accepting the folder. She spoke sharply and brusquely. Neville glanced at the twins, uneasily.

"Курагин, только. Это тарифы?" said the man. Bogdanov brushed away the man's question with a puffing of her lips.

"I believe we have - oh, Somnium - I believe we have the man you're looking for. A man named Kuragin is the only contractor in town who regularly has them run such things to the airstrip." She studied the documents in the file folder with evident distaste, as the man she'd questioned collapsed into sleep. "Lev Kuragin. Although the manifests for his shipping says that they're all 'machine parts,' this is the only person who fits your bill."

"Does it have a location there?" George asked, grunting as he dragged the man into a sitting position against one wall. Fred drew his wand and cast a quick Obliviate on the man's last five minutes.

"Yes. No trouble."

"Then you take the lead," said Neville, and Disillusioned himself. The other three followed suit, and Bogdanov led them out, clicking at intervals.

≡≡≡Ω≡≡≡

About twenty minutes later, deep into dusk, they arrived at a prefabricated construction-site trailer resting on cinder blocks. Unfinished wood paneling and two old doors had been nailed together to extend or repair one end of the trailer, which was surrounded by weeds. A green pickup truck, bleached by the elements, sat outside next to a shiny new motorbike. There was no sign in front of the low-roofed building, but a small hand-printed label on the mailbox outside read, "КУРАГИН ЭКСПОРТ / ИМПОРТ." The windows were opaque with grime, but it was still evident that a light was on and that someone was inside. Bogdanov clicked twice. It must be the place.

"Let's go around back, and go in from there," said Fred, quietly.

"Put whoever's inside to sleep, and quiz them a bit," said George.

Somehow, although they were all still invisible, the Shichinin could hear Bogdanov roll her eyes. Still, they all moved quietly out behind the trailer, foregoing the clicks at this point, before removing their Disillusionment.

"Phlogisticate," cast Neville on one end of the trailer, and then again on the other end. "Guns are stupid," he whispered to Bogdanov, turning to her.

"Agreed," replied the Russian witch.

"Quietus," said Neville, laying a thin blanket of quiet around the door of the trailer. It was a spell very limited in scope, but essential for moments like this.

"Just stay here-" said George.

"-and let us take care of this," said Fred.

"We're professionals," they said, in unison, looking very serious.

Bogdanov folded her arms, a light smile on her lips.

The trio of young men crept up to the trailer's back door. Neville tried the doorknob gingerly - it turned cleanly. He stepped to one side, and Fred and George squared off in front of the doorway, wands out and ready to breach. They nodded in unison at Neville, and Neville threw the door open with a convulsive motion.

It is important to note at this point that the Extinguishing Charm has no effect whatsoever on an angry dog.

One hundred and thirty pounds of angry muscle in the form of a mottled-brown Presa lunged into Fred, snapping for his throat, and the wizard was knocked backward into his twin's face. The two men and the dog fell into a struggling tangle. The impact and the snarling dog were all eerily silent for the first moment, then the wizard's backpedaling and kicking as they fought to escape the blunt-nosed snapping attack of the dog brought them out of the short range of the Quieting Charm, and the snarling of the creature burst out into the night.

Neville didn't waste any time taking careful aim, and fired off a hasty Stunning Hex immediately into the tangle just as Fred succeeded in landing a well-placed kick to the dog's snout. A pained yelp was frozen in the beast's throat. The dog trembled with a red glow for a moment, then fell stiffly onto its side.

"Nice one!" said Fred.

"Bloody hell!" said George, still lying on his back. "Someone's getting away!" He scrabbled for his lost wand. Through the rear of the trailer and the open front door, he could see a bald man throwing a leg over the motorbike parked out front. The man kicked the starter, and the motorbike's engine thrummed hoarsely.

Neville lurched forward to the open door, wand raised, and fired a second Stunning Hex. "Stupefy!

This time, though, luck wasn't with him. The red bolt of the stunner sizzled right over the head of the motorbike's rider, and as Neville took another step forward to fire again, his heel slid on something slick underfoot, skidding out from beneath him. He grabbed the doorway with his free hand, but still swayed in place for a moment as the motorbike jerked into motion and moved out of the narrow range of view afforded by the front door.

"Less of a nice one!" said Fred, scrambling to his feet, but Neville ignored him and sprinted forward, out into the front yard. The motorbike accelerated rapidly.

"Come on," shouted George, bursting past Neville. He threw open the door to the pale green pickup truck, climbing inside.

Fred pushed past Neville as well, running around to the other side of the cab, while George had his wand out. George squinted at the Muggle device warily, and then tapped the ignition with the tip of his wand, dubiously saying, "Alohomora?"

The ignition switch "unlocked," key or no, and the engine turned over and started. George looked almost criminally pleased.

"Go go go!" cried Neville, leaping into the bed of the truck with a vault. He stood up behind the cab and grabbed hold of the rear windows for hand-holds. The red light on the motorbike was receding rapidly away from them, down the road.

"Seen Dad do it a thousand times," said George, as he yanked firmly on the gearshift and stamped hard on one of the pedals in front of him. Nothing happened.

"Easy as pie," said Fred, turning the crank to roll down his window, in case that might help.

George took his foot off of one pedal, and slammed it down on the other. The truck's tires spun for a moment and then the vehicle caught traction and began to move rapidly backwards. "Got it!" he said, still grinning and turning to look behind him. His view was obstructed by Neville's crotch. "You're in the way, Neville!"

"Stop stop stop!" shouted Neville in reply. He clutched the roof of the truck desperately as the vehicle thumped vigorously over some stray cinder blocks and the kerb, out onto the street.

"We'll have to tell Dad about this!" called Fred, holding his wand to the dashboard in front of him and flexing his fingers for the delicate Charm of Perfect Function.

George took his foot off of the gas, and yanked on the gearshift again. The truck made a horrid squeal, sounding almost like a precisely-tooled machine being badly abused. Indeed, logic and mercy dictated that the engine should probably seize up and die, but Fred's timely spell prevented that. The truck's motor immediately became a throaty purr, and George stepped on the gas again.

As the car began to lurch forward, George turned the wheel rapidly, aligning the truck with the motorbike that was now turning out of sight at the end of the lane. George stamped on the gas as hard as he could, and the truck's engine roared.

The entirely ridiculous chase was on.

The motorbike had many advantages, though - being agile and quick to accelerate - and by the time they reached the end of the lane, it had already reached the end of the next road, and was making another turn. Even with magical enhancement and the enthusiasm of the ignorant, the truck just wasn't fast enough.

"Stupefy!" said Neville, and shot a glowing red bolt at the motorbike before it vanished from sight. He was far too distant to hit, but the escaping Muggle seemed to have been startled or confused by the stunner, since he swerved wildly and barely remained upright as he sped out of sight. Neville wasn't even sure he wanted to hit the man anyway… being stunned while going that speed stood a good risk of killing a Muggle. He pounded on the roof with his free hand to urge the truck on, but George already had the gas floored back down.

"Sure, we could have used our brooms-" said Fred, turning the knobs on the radio.

"-but what fun would that have been, honestly?" agreed George, spinning the wheel until the vehicle threatened to tilt onto one side as it went around the corner.

The motorbike zipped down the road past what appeared to be a cannery, accelerating rapidly. Neville almost tried a quick, "Accio Muggle," before remembering Cuthbert's Breathing Principle. He summoned the motorbike instead, and the white bike and its bald passenger visibly slowed. Encouraged, he did it again, even though it was a challenge just to stay in the truckbed, much less cast at the same time. The radio inside squealed hellishly, and Fred hastily started punching buttons on it, as the truck began to gain on the motorbike. Slowly, but gaining.

If they got close enough, Neville could pluck the man right up and off the bike. He holstered his wand and hammered on the roof again, leaning down to shout through the window in the rear of the truck's cab, "Get in close, I'll nab him off that thing! Can't stun him or he'll crack up all over the place!"

"Yes!" replied George, turning to look over his shoulder at Neville. "This is much safer!"

"At least we're putting him far away from Bogdanov," said Fred. "So he might not get eaten. Hold on, I know this song." He turned the volume knob on the radio.

Gotta, gotta

Keep on holdin' on

Never gonna turn you loose

I can't turn you loose

Gotta gotta - Keep on holdin' on

"That's on one of Dad's listening-dog discs," said George, delighted. He followed the motorbike around another turn, tires squealing. "That Muggle device he was always cranking during hols when we were twelve."

The motorbike's engine revved loudly, and the rider leaned forward. Neville summoned the bike again, but the Muggle motor and magical magnetism seemed to be evenly matched. Even worse, they were heading east, out of the sparsely-populated outskirts of Mikhaylovka and towards the main body of the town. Even now, they were starting to pass cars parked on the street, and occasional people turning to stare at the high-speed chase. Empty lots and dingy warehouses were turning into shops and homes, with overgrown bushes that crowded the sidewalk and cement-block walls with iron gates. Fairly well-peopled… there was the Statute of Secrecy to think about - unless they wanted to call in about ten thousand Obliviators.

The motorbike dropped in speed, and turned sharply down a street that ran almost parallel to the one the Shichinin were on. The Muggle roared off as George hit the brakes, which shrieked in protest. They had the chance to get a good look at their target for a just a moment, as they slowed down and he sped away: a slightly overweight bald man with thick black eyebrows and a terrified look on his face.

The turn carried them away from the populated areas of town once more - that made sense, Neville realized. This guy probably was only interested in escape, not in getting caught by Muggle aurors.

The truck roared after the motorbike, and they scooted over a low bridge spanning a narrow canal, whipping past parked cars and a woman walking her dog. There was an intersection ahead, and Neville saw the bald man's goal: there was some sort of construction going on, and most of the intersection was blocked off by orange-painted wooden barricades. Even the sidewalk was blocked with some orange barrels and cement pylons, presumably to stop overzealous motorists. A ragged-edged hole had consumed most of the asphalt within the barricades, and an official-looking van was parked nearby. The obstruction slowed the traffic of the automobiles through the intersection, and there was a line of seven cars waiting ahead to inch through. The bald man was going to take advantage of his broom-sized motorbike to zip through, leaving them in the dust.

"Unbreakable Charm!" he shouted through the window. His feet slid out from underneath him as he called in and the truck bumped wildly beneath him. Even with excellent balance and a death-grip on the window, he fell into the bed of the truck with a thump that was lost in the wind. He concentrated on holding on, so the constant bucking of the vehicle didn't just throw him clean out.

Fred and George must have heard him and taken his meaning, or come up with his same plan (a frequent occurrence these days), since as Neville got up on his knees, he saw Fred touch his wand to the dashboard. In almost the same moment, he saw George jerk the wheel to the right, and felt a tremendous thump as they jumped the kerb onto the sidewalk. Neville almost went flying again, and only stayed with the truck by thrusting his arm through the rear window and clutching desperately.

I can't turn you loose now

I'm in love with the prettiest thing

I never, never turn you loose now

Because of all the sweet love she brings

I can't turn you loose to nobody

'Cause I love you baby, yes I do

The biker slowed only slightly as he reached the intersection, went to the left of the lined-up cars, and threaded past oncoming traffic. He made a left turn as soon as he could, vanishing from sight.

The truck followed to the right of the lined-up cars, shuddering along the uneven sidewalk, and smashed through the orange barrels and concrete pylons. The barrels turned out to be filled with water, which plumed behind them in a spray mixed with chunks of broken concrete as the Unbreakable truck, preserved by Fred's timely charm, cannoned on through. The motorbike was back in sight in moments as the truck shrieked its way around the corner.

The Shichinin pursued their prey, leaving wreckage in their wake.

"That Charm-" said Fred.

"-won't last long!" said George.

They glanced at each other and grinned hugely. Some Muggle devices worked perfectly well, indefinitely, when charmed. When an Unbreakable Charm or a Charm of Perfect Function wore off, you could apply another one without worry. But most Muggle machines - including any that had electronics, batteries, or the like - would endure (at most) a single application unless they were carefully prepared (replacement of a lot of the Muggle workings with magical equivalents was time-consuming and laborious). As far as they knew, no one (Harry included) had yet figured out why. Whatever the cause, though, it was certain that this particular vehicle wasn't long for this world.

"And this truck-" said Fred.

"-is bollixed when it goes!" said George.

Neville, meanwhile, struggled to his feet in the bed of the truck, holding the back of the cab with a grip so tight his hands ached. He drew his wand again. "Accio motorbike! Accio motorbike!" They were almost within range of Wingardium Leviosa. "Come on, come on!"

The motorbike accelerated, the engine now a high-pitched whine as it strained against Neville's magic. They were out in the south of the town now, a long lake to their left along the road, while clapboard houses and rickety fences whipped by on their right. Neville didn't remember the layout of the town that well, but he was fairly sure that much more travel in this direction would take them clear out of Mikhaylovka entirely, back out among the fields that they saw on their aerial approach.

Give shaking mama,

I told ya I'm in love with only you

Gotta, do it baby why don't ya

I'll give ya everything you want

The road curved to the right, and then the bald man took a sharp left turn. He almost lost control of the bike, over-correcting to the right, but he managed to wrestle it back into the straight before he took a tumble. George took a lesson, and slowed down his fierce stamping of the gas pedal on the turn. They were less than fifty meters away now.

Neville, riding higher than the twins, saw what was ahead, and began scrambling for his pouch.

Fred and George saw a moment later. George began cranking down his window with one hand and pulling out his wand with the other. Fred's window was already down, and so he did his brother the favor of taking the wheel. The quality of their driving remained exactly the same, for better or worse.

The road ended in a muddy cul-de-sac two hundred meters ahead, and the fields beyond had been flooded. It must have been done earlier today - maybe they were going to graze bicorn here, next season. It was hard to tell, but it looked like as much as a foot of muck and water sat evenly in wide pools ahead, broken only by low rocky embankments.

Gotta gotta

Keep on holdin on

Never gonna turn you loose

Fred took back the wheel with his right hand, and stuck his wand out the window with the other. George leaned out of the window, brandishing his own wand. Neville had put his away, so that he could try to find that damn pouch in his robes oh no oh no why don't I keep it on my belt who cares if it doesn't look cool.

"Nevvie, hold on!" shouted George, as loudly as he could.

And that was when Neville realized that he'd come up with one obvious solution that the twins had come up with a completely different plan. But he had his pouch in hand now, and there was no way their plan would work, and so he just shrieked, "Broom!" at the pouch as hard as he could, and hoped for the best.

The motorbike buzzed off of the road and into the field ahead, sluicing through and spraying ribbons of mud and water behind him. The man barely even slowed.

"Glacius! Glacius! Glacius! Glacius! Glacius! Glacius! Glacius! " chanted the twins, simultaneously, wobbling the tips of their wands over and over. A simple spell with simple wandwork, but they felt their skulls ache with the strain of so much magic.

The mud and water of the field ahead froze, a spreading triangle of muck flash-chilled into brown and grey ice, crackling and cold. It looked as though winter had come to just one section of the field, icing it over to within twenty meters of their target.

Unfortunately, it was nothing like a flat surface, thanks to the passage of the motorbike. When the truck thumped off of the road and roared out into the field, it hit the uneven surface of one frozen slope, and skidded to the right, starting to spin. The tires thudded across frozen hillocks and waves of muddy ice, and the truck danced like it was a child's toy being dragged along a washboard. The Weasleys held onto anything they could find, and hooted wildly as the truck spun and shuddered. The world whirled around them, icy and uneven and crazed.

Neville was launched like a kite into the air, pinwheeling wildly and screaming, "I hate you twooooo!"

I can't turn you loose

The accumulated strain on the magics sustaining the truck's structure, combined with the conflict between enchantment and electronics, came to a peak. The truck's battery exploded violently, blasting open the hood, at the same instant the radio began to sizzle and shoot sparks. A hole appeared on the top of the dash, the plastic darkening and melting away, as some carefully-engineered Muggle component crackled with flames. The flaming truck spun and shook as it danced along the icy, uneven mud.

Neville was tumbling wildly, end over end, but he had presence of mind enough to clutch his broom to himself and hook his leg over it and will it to lift...

Gotta keep a grip on you

...and he swooped up (up? yes, up) into the air, orienting himself with the ground in seconds, laughing hysterically as he evened out and leaned forward, streaking towards the motorbike ahead of him like a giddy bolt of lightning.

The truck's spin slowed as it skidded out of the area that had been frozen, ice turning to slushy mud and slowing the destroyed vehicle's revolutions. Fred and George wasted no time, whooping and kicking open their doors to stagger out of the truck, sloshing around into the mud and staggering drunkenly away from the vehicle as best they could.

The radio burbled and screeched, unnaturally riven with interfering magics gone haywire, and wailed out a final line of music before dying with a last sizzle of static.

Gotta gotta keep on holdin on

"Wingardium Leviosa!" Neville cast, as he dove down over the motorbike. The rider was plucked out of his seat, legs and rear end lifted up, hands still clinging to the handlebars. The motion turned the throttle on the bike, and it revved fiercely; without the bald man's weight, the entire thing upended and tore itself out of his grasp, rolling and toppling around into the mud.

"Guns are stupid!" shouted Neville, streaking by the Muggle. The young man's mackintosh flapped around him as he flew, his brown eyes wide over his aquiline nose. "Stupefy!"

The bald man toppled sideways into the mud, rolling on his back with a squish of bubbles. Neville brought his broom around, and held himself stationary over the man. He found himself wishing that he hadn't stunned the fellow, or that the Muggle wouldn't be Obliviated of the whole experience, since there were all kinds of things he wanted to say, like "You can't run from the sinister seven!", or "Nothing's swifter than justice!"

He settled for shouting happily at Fred and George, rising up from the broom to call, "Do you think we can fit Muggle trucks in our pouches, so we can do that again sometime?"

"Yes, it looked like quite a ride. Quite a spectacle," said the empty air above Neville, in the voice of Ilya Bogdanov. The Russian witch materialized with a wavering in the air, sitting placidly on her broom, as she dismissed her Disillusionment. Neville started violently, his wand already pointing at her in the instinctive defense of a trained duelist before he could consciously lower his guard.

Bogdanov didn't react, only circling her broom around to face him squarely, and adding sardonically, "It has been, oh, just delightful following you three idiots and cleaning up the mess so that we don't start some sort of war."

"Huh," said Fred, who was flying sedately over, dripping with mud and water and delight. "The Director thought you might help with avoiding that, actually."

"Good on him," said George. "I feel bad about the tea, now."

"Eh?" said Bogdanov, shifting to face them. Her short grey hair was disheveled, and the footbars and grips on her broom had been changed out - she must have been flying hard. But she was smiling.

"He'll forgive us-" said Fred, shrugging.

"-once he gets off the loo," finished George.

≡≡≡Ω≡≡≡

The bald man, as it turns out, was none other than Lev Kuragin himself, the gentleman who had been shipping crates out of the town by air. And naughty Lev had been using temporary shell companies to buy serious weaponry from old Russian Army buddies. While he was happy to sell the resulting crates of weapons and ammunition to any buyer he could trust, he had found that the Ogaden National Liberation Front would pay a premium. Lev had found that the ONLF would even grease his palm if he shipped weapons to any other militant groups in or around Ethiopia, particularly since the 1995 Ethiopian elections that had pushed the ONLF out of power. An unstable country was to the advantage of the violent political minority, which was working to seize power once more.

Lev even knew the source of their money: vast funds fraudulently drawn from World Bank development efforts in Ethiopia, that had been intended for the area around Calub, as well as five wealthy Cairo financiers. And he'd been extremely willing to tell them names, addresses, and specific numbers.

Veritaserum was a wonderful thing.

After the Shichinin and Bogdanov dropped Kuragin off at the edge of town, replete with new memories to account for a missing night and morning - and a few to ensure a change of heart when it came to the arms trade - they made ready to return home, Apparating back to Volgograd and the local Domovoi. They had been concerned about having a good story ready for the sleepy-looking man with the wet mustache, but he'd stamped their documents as disinterestedly as he'd given them entrance.

Fred got out the portkey back to the Ministry lobby, holding it up. It was the broken stub of a child's plastic meterstick, in keeping with the principle that a portkey should look completely uninteresting (or even unpleasant) to casual Muggle inspection.

"Well then-" he said.

"-that was fun." George said.

"I hope it was not too boring for you, Madame Bogdanov," said Neville, taking hold of the portkey as well.

"It was actually… quite amusing, I must admit, gentlemen. Quite a bit more exciting than my current post, even if the goals here are even sillier." The Russian witch smiled again, and put her hand on theirs.

George and Fred glanced at each other.

"You know, there are five Egyptians who have been spreading money to very bad places," said George.

"We'll probably be going after them, next. We'll need someone who speaks Arabic," said Fred.

"And I can see many interesting philosophical discussions, waiting to be had…" said Neville, grinning. "How about it?"

Bogdanov sighed, and shrugged. "Why not?" She put her hand on the portkey, and leaned over to look Fred dead in the eye. "After all, I know a place in Cairo that serves an excellent fillet of Muggle."

Fred opened his mouth to say something, but she snapped the portkey, and the four of them vanished.

Chapter 22: Gholas

The Guild navigators, gifted with limited prescience, had made the fatal decision: they'd chosen always the clear, safe course that leads ever downward into stagnation.

-Frank Herbert, Dune

≡≡≡Ω≡≡≡

"Innervate. Innervate."

Lawrence Bradwian and Annabeth Dankgesang slumped onto the chairs that had been set behind them, their rigid bodies relaxing. "Just relax a moment, children," Harry said, from where he sat at the meeting table. "You're in the Tower, but you're fine. You were just stunned."

He glanced up at them, then returned his gaze to the book open before him. He turned a page, slowly, and his unoccupied fingers fiddled with the end of his ponytail, where it lay over his shoulder to curl under his chin. Auror Kwannon stood behind and to one side of the pair of students, watching them as she put away her wand.

"Feeling all right, Mr. Bradwian?" The boy nodded. He was an athletic boy, with striking features… perhaps Middle Eastern descent? Close-cut black hair clung in curls to his head, and his eyes were a mellow brown. Harry thought he remembered the boy's mother was from the Sawad.

"And you, Miss…?" Harry said, looking to the other student. She was a small girl, with black skin and tightly-twisted, short dreadlocks. She seemed very calm.

She cleared her throat, but spoke clearly, "Annabeth Dankesang."

"Well then, Mr. Bradwian… Ms. Dankesang…. I am Dean of the Science Program here at Hogwarts, Harry Potter-Evans-Verres. I don't believe we've had occasion to meet," said Harry, glancing back down at his book. He could hear the breath catch in Lawrence's throat at the introduction. Harry looked up again. "You brought your classmate here… Samuel Meroveni-Bowles."

Lawrence nodded, collecting himself, and he looked concerned, pursing his lips and raising his eyebrows. "Yes, sir. He fell after Div and P, and... it was bad, sir. I didn't think we could… well, Madame Pomfrey is wonderful, but like the song says, 'when in doubt, stick it out.' " The boy was quoting a promotional jingle the Tower had used a few years ago. "Is Sammy all right?"

"Oh, yes," said Harry. He watched the two children closely as he turned another page of his book, adding, "In fact, he's already back in his own bed in Ravenclaw Tower."

He could see the small muscles in the boy's cheeks flex as his jaw tightened. Annabeth did better, but her eyes opened wide despite her best efforts.

"You might be wondering why I wanted to speak to you, Lawrence and Annabeth. The reason is actually a bit embarrassing… it's been brought to my attention over the past hour that you did me quite a good turn last year, and I never thanked you. I would have done so if I'd known, of course," Harry said. He turned his head so that his ponytail would slip off his shoulder, out of sight behind him. "I had a question, first, though."

"Of course, sir," said Annabeth.

"Well, then… I suppose I'll start off by saying that I don't believe in cruelty, so we'll just out with it now: you're pinched. Caught. Discovered. I have had people toy with me too often when they had some small measure of power over me, often in the form of information I needed, and so I don't have much liking for it. So it's best you know straightaway. I'll give you a moment to think about that and decide if you believe me." Harry looked back down at the book and read the page before him as the seconds passed, stretching uncomfortably. After a minute, he finally looked up again. The two students were sitting still, hands folded in their laps. Lawrence looked like was trying to swallow with a dry mouth.

"I must confess that you will feel quite stupid, very shortly. I'm sorry about that," said Harry. "But before we get there, my question: why in Merlin's name did you think it would be okay to badly injure - very nearly kill - your classmate, just to get what you want?" He paused, and clucked his tongue thoughtfully. "Or maybe: why did you think I would think that was okay? Surely you at least considered your plan might go wrong? Didn't you stop to think of the possible consequences?"

"I'm not sure what you mean, sir," said Lawrence. His voice warbled on the second word, and he looked worried.

Wise not to try to appear calm, little Larry, nor indignant. But an innocent student would just be confused. Maybe it's because people worry so much about being caught for the things we've really done that we tend to be completely baffled by false accusation.

"Auror Kwannon, how many people are stepped-down in the clinic right now, in hold?" Harry said, turning to her and leaning to rest his chin on one hand.

Kwannon reached into her pocket and pulled out a small brown abacus, identical to the one on the table. She consulted it for a moment. "Four, sir. Not too many in Receiving or being treated, either. Slow day."

Harry turned and looked steadily at the students once more. Annabeth's mouth had opened slightly and Lawrence looked nauseous, as if he'd been kicked in the stomach. Harry supplemented the effect by shoving one of the parchments in front of him towards the pair, with its decoded - and obviously false - message.

THECUPISNOTENOUGHWEMUSTADDTOOURCOLLECTIONIBELIEVETHATMANYITEMSOFGREATPOWERAREHELDINTHETOWERPREPARETHEPLANWESPOKEABOUTBEFOREANDWEWILLCOMMUNICATEWITHTHEABACUS

The abacuses were used in the clinic to track the flow of patients. Harry waited a moment for the magnitude of their mistake to sink into the pair.

"You had some clever ideas. But while the tactics were clever, the strategy didn't really make much sense," Harry continued. "You were operating at an information deficit, and you knew that, and still didn't account for it."

"But if the abacus is…" Annabeth said, brow furrowing. Harry was able to watch her as her thoughts progressed, and he wondered if this was what it had been like to deal with himself as a child… cleverness and innovation trapped inside of a fishbowl-sized world, unable to grasp the limits of their perspective and experience. When you can only see a handful of moving parts, the machine of the world looked so simple and easy to manipulate. He remembered his stumbling horror when he'd been given occasion to see the workings laid bare, in all their complexity and danger.

"Yes, you understand, I see," said Harry. Lawrence's pallor looked distinctly yellowish, but he still seemed more confused than horrified. Slower on the uptake. Harry addressed himself to Annabeth, who was clearly the brains of the operation (such as that might be) and the leader of the duo. "So then: it seems as though you attempted to murder young Sammy, with whom you've had some problems in the past. You've been stunned for about five hours, now, and I had a chance to speak to your victim, your Headmistress, and Director Diggory of the DMLE."

Harry closed the book, a little more forcefully than necessary. "When I was your age, I took it as a great offense that no one did me the courtesy of dealing with me directly unless I forced the issue. So then, let me be direct: you have been idiots on a scale that you cannot yet fully appreciate. Not only was your plan unlikely to work, you thought it was wise to try to use it to frame a classmate - a boy who has been involved in some dark dealings indeed with the rest of his family, some of whom were expelled for their pains, but who didn't do anything wrong here."

He stood now, rising and placing both palms on the table in front of him, looking down on the two students with cold green eyes. "You are said to be 'Silver Slytherins,' but I wonder if that little faction of Draco's has turned out to mean anything at all in his absence. He told me, once, that it was about the purity of truth - that he'd learned that truth was the most important thing, even when plotting, since if you didn't know the reality of the world then you couldn't affect it, no matter how brilliantly effective your plans might otherwise be. That's why you need both instrumental rationality - acting based on truth - and epistemic rationality - knowing what is true. They are both necessary if you want things to happen as you desire."

Lawrence had rallied, now. Harry imagined the boy forcing down his nausea and searching for an escape. The boy forced himself upright in the chair and thrust out his chin, saying, "But that's the very reason why we acted… we knew the truth, and wanted to act on it. The Meroveni-Bowles are no good and-"

"And you wanted to make your enemy pay for something, even if you couldn't make him pay for his real crimes. What was it that he'd done, exactly, Mr. Bradwian?" said Harry, and now his voice was as cold as his eyes.

"He and his family tried to kill Turm, just because they were ashamed of what their father had done - because they were ashamed of their half-brother. They tried to kill him," said Lawrence. The boy rose up slightly out of his seat as he spoke, taking strength from his indignation. "They stole potion ingredients from Hogwarts, from Professor Slughorn's stores and the greenhouses, so that they could supply Ragged Rooncrown and his Euphoric distribution in Knockturn Alley! They tried to steal Helga Hufflepuff's Cup from Smith Manor - and that's wrong, even if it turns out you did it, sir! And Sammy tried to kill me in a duel when Annabeth and I stopped the Meroveni-Bowles! His sister and brother were expelled, but he managed to get out of all the trouble for everything, just because they took the blame!" Now he was standing, and Harry noticed that Lawrence was actually his same height, so that Harry had to stand up straight and stop leaning on the table in order to look the boy in the eyes. Maybe he should make himself taller. Auror Kwannon had moved to one side and drawn her wand, clearing her line of sight, though her wand remained casually at her side.

Lawrence was incensed now, having worked himself up into enough outrage to serve as a shield from his shock and fear. The boy's clear young eyes were narrowed in anger. He lifted a finger and jabbed it in Harry's direction. "And Sammy was never going to die, since I was waiting at the bottom of the stairs to catch him with Wingardium Leviosa. No one saw that, but veritaserum can prove it." He lowered his hand. "I stopped him from falling so fast, and I saved his life. But he needed to pay for what he's done. I wasn't doing anything but justice."

"Samuel Meroveni-Bowles comes from an unpleasant family, but he has not, to my knowledge, done anything more than get dragged along with his older brother and sister and be bullied into helping them occasionally. Questioning under veritaserum revealed a scared boy in a bad clan trying to muddle his way through… rather a different picture than you'd paint in defense of your actions. The child has not earned a brutal beating and near-death experience, even if you managed to stop yourself short of giving him an execution." Harry looked at Lawrence, coldly and with clear contempt. Annabeth had leaned forward and buried her face in her hands, and was crying quietly. "You are badly in need of a lesson on losing… a lesson I once had to learn, as it happens, but one which I have no time to teach at the moment."

Harry pushed back his chair and walked to the end of the table, where two wands were sitting. He picked up Lawrence's in one hand, then looked back at its owner. "To your great good fortune, Prior Incantato showed that you did help arrest the vicious fall that you caused. And to your even greater fortune, no lasting harm appears to have been done. Sammy doesn't remember anything. But you are a thuggish young pair, and stupid. You have brutalized a boy in an act of vigilantism because you were sure he was guilty though you had no proof - the swan song of so many thugs, who always manage to make themselves the true hero or victim."

Lawrence sagged back into his chair, his bravado evaporating like the bluff that it was. He stared ahead of himself, and Harry knew that consequences and dread were playing out in his head.

"You have been bullies - stupid ones. You have brought shame to your families and your House and to whatever the Silver Slytherins might be, these days, besides a fashionable social club. I want you to understand that, Lawrence and Annabeth. Where you're going, you will need that understanding. You will need that lesson to make you strong."

Annabeth began crying even harder, her shoulders shaking, and Lawrence slumped forward, gripping the arms of his chair spasmodically. He looked about ready to cry. Harry waited. Not to be cruel, but because he knew from experience that it was very difficult to change who you were. They needed to sit there with bile rising in their throats, tears burning hotly in their eyes, seeing their entire futures burning around them… and they needed to know that they weren't being oppressed.

Harry knew that it was a difficult thing to realize that you'd never really been the hero, all along - to know that you were some form of lesser villain, deluded and stupid in your villainy - somehow even less than the honest evil, since you rewarded yourself with misplaced righteousness. Let them see the tears of their mothers waiting in the future, the bitter scorn of Headmistress McGonagall, the tall walls of Howard Prison.

"You will need that lesson, because you are going to help me with something," Harry said. "The world is changing quickly these days, and a great many very smart people have convinced me that my previous strategy hasn't been working…. so you are going to help me with a new one."

"One constrains the partner's choice by constraining one's own behavior," Schelling had written in The Strategy of Conflict. "The object is to set up for one's self and communicate persuasively to the other play a mode of behavior (including conditional responses to the other's behavior) that leaves the other a simple maximization problem whose solution for him is the optimum for one's self, and to destroy the other's ability to do the same."

In other words, strategically limit one's own courses of action to only allow for the ones you prefer, so your enemy must either allow you to move unmolested, or else move against you in one of the styles you've chosen for them - since by limiting your own available responses, you've limited their ability to provoke you to unfavorable action.

"You are going to join the Honourable, Lawrence and Annabeth," Harry said. He dropped Lawrence's wand on the table. "It was you two who helped my people discover where the Cup of Helga Hufflepuff was being stored, secretly mewed up in Hepzibah Smith's house after her death, so I know you can be of some use. And perhaps now you understand your weaknesses in terms of strategy. And maybe in time, you might even understand the value of life and the price of pain, and why I have dedicated my existence to preserving the one and preventing the other."

"We can't be spies," Lawrence said, dully. He turned to stare at Harry. "I'm only fifteen."

"I have good reason to think that your ages will help make you excellent spies, in this case, Mr. Bradwian. I have a plot in mind to improve the world, or at least one small corner of it, and you are an absolutely necessary part of that," said Harry. The Dean of the Science Program returned to his seat, where the book he'd been reading lay on the table in front of him. "I will give you instructions on how to get started. We will not be meeting for a while, I'm afraid. Pip will be in touch, though." Harry picked up the book again, and opened it back to the page where he'd left off. "I'm not asking, of course. But I don't see how my little plot could work without you, and with your callous stupidity and violence you've forfeited a great deal." He looked down at the page, and resumed reading. "I think one day you'll understand, if it's any consolation. Goodbye."

Kwannon stepped forward, now, gesturing at Lawrence to get up. The boy did, as slowly and gingerly as if he were afraid of breaking something. He gently put a hand under Annabeth's elbow, and guided her to her feet, as well. She didn't stop crying, keeping her face hidden. The auror escorted the children out of the room, pausing only to collect their wands.

Harry returned to God-Emperor of Dune, and read quietly for some time.

Chapter 25: Press Pass

I'm not sure what I expected to find in Siegfried's, the latest dining establishment in Diagon Alley. It's widely whispered that Tower money helped put the gilt on the doorknobs, so to speak, but even knowing that, I didn't expect quite the level of opulence one finds at this adventurous new experiment in "Muggle fine dining." It appears that the Man-Who-Was-the-Boy-Who-Lived spared no expense: from your first step to your last bite, Siegfried's is an experience in luxury. Such an investment might simply have been necessary, since "Muggle" and "fine dining" is almost a contradiction in terms. But the Tower, and Mr. Siegfried König, seem to be determined to change that by rubbing their wealth in your face through Siegfried's well-appointed interiors.

The service was also a study in excellence. The waitstaff were courteous and helpful as they explained the odder aspects of the meal. Novelties in the vocabulary they employed include: "sous vide," "liquid nitrogen," and "emulsifier." The only thing missing from their careful explanation was any information whatsoever; I still have no idea how my food was prepared, except that some manner of Muggle mysticism was involved. I declined a kitchen tour, as it sounded dangerous.

For all that the decorating was ostentatious and the explanation of the menu was inane, however, I must admit that the food was a revelation of flavor and texture. Even when I didn't understand it, I enjoyed it. I tried a chutney that was complex and rich, but balanced perfectly with quail eggs in a bed of a squash paste. I found that it was…

-Excerpted from "New 'Muggle Restaurant' Opens Its Doors in Britain," by Sylvia de Kamp in American Mage.

≡≡≡Ω≡≡≡

Margaret Bulstrode pushed open the door to Billie's Bobbing Bubbies with some distaste. Just touching the greenish metal handle made her feel dirty, and the scene inside didn't make her feel much better. A corpulent man with pointed ears was standing at the front counter, paging through the thick catalogue of the memories on offer, while the balding woman who was working there was digging under her fingernails with the pointed tip of a decorative glass stopper from a nearby phial. A very pale man with lank grey hair completed the scene, sitting at one of the small tables in the waiting area and eating from a ludicrously large bowl of apples 'n onions - the smell of which was filling the room with cloying sweetness. Everything seemed like it was covered with a thin film of filth.

Yuck.

Margaret didn't say anything to any of the three people, but only continued on straight to the little bobbing rooms. Three of them had closed doors, indicating that they were occupied, but a fourth had a crude sign fixed to it: OUT OF ORDER. She opened it anyway, and closed it behind her.

As promised, there was no Pensieve inside, only a swoop-armed Art Noveau chair with a threadbare cushion, and an empty metal rack where the magical device had once stood. Margaret gathered up the folds of her robe - it was a nice once, too, all fresh with sharp folds - and gingerly sat down on the chair.

She waited almost a full minute. The Goddess was in Knockturn Alley, and Margaret needed to be careful of her. She wasn't doing anything wrong, necessarily, but… one could never tell. In fact, Margaret had seen the glamorous villainess herself just ten minutes ago when she was on her way to Billie's: Hermione Granger had been with her gang of thugs, harassing some poor shopkeeper The sighting had so rattled Margaret that she'd been stumbling over her feet the entire rest of the walk here, and very nearly went tumbling in an undignified fashion after tripping on some hidden edge of the road a few minutes later.

But no one else entered the establishment, so it appeared she hadn't been followed.

"Freedom from tyrants, the strength of individuality, and the traditions of wizardkind," she said. She spoke quietly, as though to the air, and braced herself.

The chair trembled underneath her, and then with a violent jerk it flipped itself backwards. It pivoted as though fixed in the air, and her legs flew up and she tumbled over, and she gasped in alarm (every time!). But rather than being deposited on the floor just behind the chair, Margaret was sliding back into a space that hadn't been there before, and in a trice she was dropped gently onto a wooden platform at the end of a long hallway.

She caught her breath and fixed her robes and hair. For some reason the process had a tendency to lodge the back edge of your robe inside the waistband of your pants or knickers, so it paid to take a moment and collect yourself. Margaret suspected that was a subtlety of Draco's devising. He called the password to enter (freedom, strength, traditions) a "priming process," saying that it was good to remind yourself of your goals every time you set to work, and she couldn't help but imagine that it suited his inscrutable purposes to discomfit every visitor's clothing, as well, to prime them for being embarrassed.

Once she was ready, Margaret took a deep breath and walked to the end of the hall, making her face bold and her step even bolder. Confidence could carry you far. She pushed through the door, and stopped just within. Not quite striking a pose, but just an entrance moment.

She needn't have bothered. No Draco, no Narcissa, no Shacklebolt. Just that wretched Muggle-lover Edgar Erasmus, the insufferably priggish auror Gregor Nimue, that American writer whose name Margaret couldn't remember, and some boy she'd never met. No one she really needed to impress…

No, no… that's Stupid Slytherin thinking. A Silver Slytherin doesn't turn up her nose at any chance to cultivate power, no matter what "sort" of person is their potential ally, she thought, admonishing herself. It was a weird way of thinking, almost unnatural: an entirely different level. Beyond dominating or controlling people, even beyond fooling them… searching for the utility of each person, regardless of their inferiorities. A pure Slytherin, a true Slytherin in the tradition of the old heirs of that house, they knew that the important thing was to win. Everything else was a hobby.

"Hullo," Margaret said to the room.

Nimue didn't bother to rise from his chair, but only glanced up at her and nodded. He was sitting at the long and narrow table that dominated the room, and had seven parchments arrayed in front of him, neatly, so that they were all visible.

Erasmus, who was sitting next to Nimue, was a little more polite. He rose to his feet and inclined his head to her. "Margaret."

The writer - Sylvia de Kamp! that was her name! - was sitting with the boy at the other end of the table, and didn't appear to notice her entrance, keeping her eyes fixed on the young man. The boy had his back to Margaret, and he turned just enough so that she could see his face (handsome, with beautiful skin and a look of misery) before returning his attention to Sylvia. She was a beautiful but cold-looking woman, with no charm to her tight blonde bun or sharp cheekbones.

Margaret glanced around the room. A Floo chimney was along one wall, installed illegally and at great expense on a private network. A stuffed owl resided on the mantle above, next to a jar of Floo Powder. A sofa and a pair of chairs sat before it, all upholstered in the most luxuriously soft bicorn leather. A narrow hole was visible in the ceiling above the chairs, where a simple covered pipe up to the roof could admit owls. All along another wall, to her left and right, were stacked wooden boxes. They must contain the latest edition of Unbreakable Honour, waiting for Narcissa to arrange the shipping.

"Edgar," said Margaret, approaching the big, red-haired man. She straightened her posture slightly, putting her shoulders back as she folded her hands into her sleeves. "Is Kingsley here? I brought two more Time-Turners, but I'm only supposed to give them to him."

Erasmus settled back into his seat, shaking his head as he did so. He was in sleeveless potioneer robes. "No, he's not. Two of my people are in the laboratory, and Gem is making Euphoric down the hall." He gestured at the door to the hall, on the other side of the room. "I'm glad he's not here, he'd just be bothering me. Leave the Turners with… oh, with Gregor, or someone." He nodded his head to indicate the Tower auror sitting beside him. "No, he is assisting me… just give those here, then." He held out a large florid hand.

Erasmus was well-built and supposedly brilliant, but couldn't really sort out where he stood on a lot of important things… Muggles, most of all. He talked a good game about the natural order, but he was also always neck-deep into some Muggle book or other (or sometimes two or three books, Muggle and magical both, while he muttered and made notes). Draco might also use science, but you didn't have to worry about his loyalties. Erasmus… well, he just only seemed to care about the bastardized magical research he did with science in his little crypto-alchemical laboratory here.

"No, sorry. I can't do that. No reflection on you, of course, Edgar, but orders are orders," Margaret said, smiling apologetically.

Draco didn't tolerate that sort of rank stupidity. Not that he'd do anything really terrible to her, but he wouldn't ever trust her again if she was so cavalier about such things. And his anger could be terrible… she'd heard rumors of punishments to traitors. The Windowpain Curse, for example. A victim who looked at the black square of a window at night - any window, any night - would be cursed to always see an apparition looking back at him: a pale, wide-eyed face with large and sharp teeth, staring back at him from the darkness. Nothing more… but always that. She couldn't imagine who'd come up with that… what sort of person would even think that way. Just hearing about that one had made her afraid to open the curtains at night.

Erasmus shrugged and placed his hand back on the table. Nimue just glanced up and smirked, then returned his gaze to the parchments. Margaret stepped over behind the two, to look between them at the subject of their interest. "Research, Edgar?"

"Looking for a pattern in seeming miscellanea," said Erasmus. "Trying to… verify, shall we say." He glanced over at the miserable-looking boy. The boy didn't look over.

Report from the Office of the Tower Ombudsman

Our office has determined that by far the largest vulnerability, flaw, or weakness in the Tower continues to be the reliance on a single figurehead and leader, Harry Potter-Evans-Verres. While his prestige and reputation remain one of the driving forces behind the popularity of Tower programs and initiatives, in addition to their own dramatic results and merits, he represents what Security Director Alastor Moody said in an interview was a "single point of failure."

We also have...

Margaret, surprised to see an internal memo rather than some obscure line of research, looked to another parchment.

Memorandum from Councilor Regulus Hig of the Mystical and Benevolent Council of Westphalia

Mr. Potter:

Hope you are well. Have checked on your question re number of wizards with certain groups here. Numbers attached. Please note they bear out my argument. Many generations of wizards have moved to Britain over past centuries, draining blood and talent from elsewhere. Must be effect, not the other way around, given last years immigration numbers (attached, next sheet). Seems clear that my reasoning stands; in final agreement, Tower will endow chairs at RI and SWI. Partial compensation for generations of drain. Yes? Please reply.

Re representative: not sure who to trust with proxy these days. Limpel had maybe dozen in her org, or more. A dozen total now have turned up with minds wiped. Would suggest distance collaboration, but understand Tower protocol prevents communication. Will think on it.

Be well

Reg

The string of numbers that followed was rather beyond her curiosity's scope. She'd never been forced to take Arithmancy, thank Merlin, since she graduated the year before it became mandatory. Millicent wouldn't stop complaining about it, a few years ago.

She glanced over at the next parchment, frowning. What was all this?

Harry:

Quick note on where we are.

No good results from Hopkirk. She says it's not a problem of obscurity, but that there's just too many results. Three is a number of power. There were three witches who were famous Scottish seers in the sixteenth century, there were three Peverell brothers and three Deathly Hallows, the ancient Greek Herpo found three ways to hide from murder, there were three towers of Atlantis in legend… Too many threes. Hopkirk will keep looking, but says it could mean anything. I don't think you should rely on much insight until we have more details.

Some descriptions of the transportation magic described by Hermione. Väinämöinen wrote about a horse of flame was used to bear brave warriors to the battlefield. Not sure if any wards can be devised without more details and experimentation. Right now, Tineagar or whoever could pop right into Howard or Hogwarts or Whitehall.

I'll work more on this, and get back to Tuesday. This feels unfair, though… piled on top of Malfoy and his stupid Honourable. Hope Hermione knocks them off their high horse.

Cedric

"The Goddess is after us now… for real? Like, she's done swanning about the world and having people kiss her ring? Is that why she's here?" Margaret asked with rising alarm. She believed in the cause and all that, but she'd already been through one interrogation. She wasn't interested in repeating the experience… Mad-Eye Moody shouting at her and demanding she confess to helping with the Diagon Alley bombing, always acting just crazy enough that you had to wonder if he might snap if you didn't just confess... Margaret shuddered. Thank Merlin for Amycus Carrow, who'd been by her side the entire time. Pervy, but effective.

"She's here?" asked Erasmus, looking up at her again. "In London?" Even Nimue was paying attention to her now, and Sylvia and the boy with whom she was speaking had stopped their conversation and were staring.

"She's here in Knockturn," said Margaret. "She was-"

"You little fool," snarled Nimue, leaping to his feet. "You didn't think to say?!"

Erasmus gathered all the parchments up into a bundle, knocking the table violently as he stood up. "Gregor, why didn't you know about this?!" He opened his robes, but before he could stuff the parchments inside, Nimue snatched them away.

"Shut up! They don't tell me everything… not when they're suspicious!" said Nimue in an angry hiss, folding the parchments up and drawing his wand. At the other end of the table, Sylvia had drawn her own, and she and the boy were both standing.

"My research!" cried Erasmus, bustling over to the door to the hall and disappearing. A clatter of beakers soon sounded from that direction, as the worried researcher rushed to save his work.

"But she's not knocking at the door or anything," said Margaret, upset by the reaction. She took a step back, and drew her wand, although she wasn't sure why. "She's just in Knockturn, why do you think-"

"What other bloody reason would the Goddess have for coming to Knockturn but to look for us?" demanded Nimue. "It's not even a question - can't believe you're even allowed in here, what is Draco thinking?!" He turned to Sylvia. "Get going! Take Lawrence and finish the damn interview later!"

The American writer was already pulling the boy towards the hearth, almost dragging him by wrist. She whispered her definition, but had time enough to shoot Margaret a look of contempt before the pair were gone in a burst of green flame.

"But I think you're over-reacting," said Margaret helplessly. "How would she even-"

"I was at Azkaban when Hermione Granger broke it like a child's toy!" snapped Nimue, darting over to one of the crates along the wall and snatching up a satchel that was sitting on it. "She has died and come back and she is not human. Do you know the stories they tell in the DMLE? One of the Weasley idiots saw her put that author fellow - Lockhart - saw her put him through a wall with her bare hands, after she found out some nastiness he'd been up to. A Hogwarts wall!"

"Gilderoy Lockhart? But he's not in any trouble… he just published-" stammered Margaret.

"Why am I even wasting time with you! Stay and risk your neck, it's…" Nimue trailed off as he saw the stuffed owl on the chimney mantle start to flap its wings and hoot. Without another word, the Tower auror leapt to the hearth, and was gone in his own flash of green flame.

"Edgar!" called out Margaret. "The owl!" She didn't wait for a reply, but just concentrated on the three Ds. Let the idiot and those stupid Euphoric-makers fend for themselves.

Godric's Hollow, she thought, clearly and with force. Then she tapped herself on the head with the curious wiggle motion of Apparition.

Nothing.

Oh, Merlin, there's wards. They've locked it down with an Anti-Disapparition Jinx. She turned to the chimney. That was the way out, no matter what wards… that was it's whole purpose. "Edgar!" she shrieked, running over to the chimney. "She's really here!" She snatched a handful of Floo Powder from the jar on the mantel, and threw it into the fire, which turned emerald.

"Borgin and Burkes," she said, and stepped into the flames. She'd go to the other hide-out and escape from there.

Nothing.

"They cut us off!" said Erasmus from behind her. "Oh… oh… what… oh…," he stammered. She turned to see the big wizard charging across the room, awkwardly bundling three big boxes as he went. A fourth box followed him, floating along by flapping transparent silvery wings. "We'll have to use the owl-bolt," he said, peering up at the narrow passage. She stepped out of the flames.

Three other men burst into the room from the same door Erasmus had used. She recognized Geoffrey Gem and his two cronies: the suppliers of local Euphorics. Gem was a rail-thin man with terrible teeth - all snaggly and yellow - and thinning hair. Each of the three potioneers had a smock on and was carrying a clinking crate of phials. "Hold up, Eggy!" called Gem.

Erasmus put down his boxes and pointed his wand at the narrow hole meant for owls. "We're going, Geoff," he said.

There was a loud booming sound, as though someone up in Billie's Bouncing Bubbies had knocked over a heavy piece of furniture.

"Just need to take down the wards, then we can punch out through the roof," said Erasmus, concentrating. His already reddish complexion turned downright scarlet as he worked, and sweat was visible on his brow.

There was another heavy boom from upstairs. Margaret found that she was clutching her wand so tightly that her fingers ached, and forced herself to relax. "Hurry, Edgar!"

"These aren't supposed to be easy to take down," he snapped, but he gritted his teeth and squinted as he worked even harder.

"They can't get in here for hours… hours of magic to stop them from burning in," mewled Gem. Margaret almost laughed in his face.

There was a third boom, and this one not only echoed in the room with an accompanying shattering sound as something broke, but the furniture actually shifted. Margaret turned to face the entry door. "That sounded like-"

The center of the door cracked as something hit it from the other side, the wood splitting from top to bottom. One of Gem's assistants dropped a crate, and it hit the ground with a crash of breaking glass. "Oh Merlin," the man said, swaying in place. The rich and sweet smell of shrivelfig filled the room.

There was another crashing sound, and a golden fist appeared, spearing out through the door and sending chips of wood into the air. It opened and seized one side of the broken door, and then thick golden fingers pulled until Margaret heard the metal of hinges squeal and give way. The remains of the door fell apart and open, and the Goddess stepped through. She wore a golden gauntlet on her left hand, and wielded her wand in her right. The metal of the gauntlet glinted brightly, like it was forged from sunlight. It looked very dangerous. She was flanked by a scowling, short witch and a buxom, taller one, both of whom were also wearing golden gauntlets, and a spectacled man who looked a bit scared. A floating Quotes Quill followed the man.

"Edgar," said the Goddess. "We need to talk."